<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latitudes Online Exhibitors Feed</title>
    <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor</link>
    <description>Exhibitors metaobjects for Doofinder</description>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_givan_ltz-2</g:id>
      <title>Givan Lötz</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_givan_ltz-2</link>
      <description>Givan Lötz is a contemporary artist known for his pioneering use of encaustic (wax) painting. His gestural, non-literal “matterscapes” explore nature’s cycles of growth, decay, and renewal, expressing a dialogue between landscape and emotional response rather than literal depiction. Lötz’s work seeks enchantment and resonance in the natural world, creating a personal visual language that reflects both inner states and the regenerative rhythms of the environment.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Givan_Lotz_2e2ab789-d4be-4b5c-b4be-6ef12740bfdf.jpg?v=1756734677</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:27:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_natasha_evans-2</g:id>
      <title>Natasha Evans</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_natasha_evans-2</link>
      <description>Natasha (b. 1978, Zimbabwe; raised in Zambia) is a Lusaka-based mixed-media artist. She holds a BA (Hons) in Illustration from The Arts Institute at Bournemouth and works from her home studio. Her practice blends abstraction and figuration across paper, canvas, and sculptural materials like calabash, cement, and textiles. Natasha explores African identity, womanhood, and the dualities of existence, using metaphor, symbolism, and experimental techniques such as photographic transfers, mark-making, and layering. She has exhibited locally and internationally, including Paris, and continues to develop new work.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Natasha_Evans.png?v=1756736450</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:27:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_puleng_mongale-1</g:id>
      <title>Puleng Mongale</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_puleng_mongale-1</link>
      <description>Puleng Mongale (b. 1991, Durban, South Africa) is a contemporary visual artist working in photography and digital media. Her practice explores spirituality, identity, belonging, and womanhood, using art to process lived experiences and assert her narrative. Mongale’s work has been featured in exhibitions including Africa Foto Fair, Abidjan (2023); The Fold, London (2021); and Terrains of Possibility, Lagos (2021), as well as online and local group shows.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Puleng_Mongale.png?v=1756736830</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:27:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_jana_hamman-1</g:id>
      <title>Jana Hamman</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_jana_hamman-1</link>
      <description>Jana Hamman is a South African designer, creative director, and artist working across digital, mixed media, and installation. A 2005 BA Information Design graduate from the University of Pretoria, she uses humour, irony, and satire to explore societal norms. Her practice balances personal curiosity and play with collaborative projects, creating work that entertains and engages audiences.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Jana_Hamman.png?v=1756735073</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:27:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_wessel_hamman-1</g:id>
      <title>Wessel Hamman</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_wessel_hamman-1</link>
      <description>Wessel Hamman (b. 1954, Pretoria) is a painter and designer whose practice explores clarity in visual communication. Using masking techniques, he creates figurative works reminiscent of stained-glass saints and Andy Warhol’s hero worship, portraying both cultural icons and anonymous faces. Juxtaposed with graffiti screen prints, his work interrogates notions of celebrity, accessibility, and relevance in an age of fast fame.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Wessel_Hamman.png?v=1756738086</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:27:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_eleven_editions-1</g:id>
      <title>Eleven Editions</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_eleven_editions-1</link>
      <description>Founded by artist Bevan de Wet in 2016, Eleven Editions is a collaborative printmaking studio located in the historic downtown district of Ferreirasdorp, Johannesburg. As an artist-run workshop, we partner with a diverse range of South African and international artists to publish and develop innovative print and paper-based projects. Our studio has a primary focus on etching, relief printing, and various monoprinting media, with a strong emphasis on experimentation and combining different disciplines. We also host regular public workshops in techniques ranging from etching and marbling to bookbinding, fostering a wider appreciation for the printmaking craft. Eleven Editions is proud to have collaborated with many of the country&apos;s most respected artists, including Norman Catherine, Walter Oltmann, and Diane Victor. The exceptional works produced in our studio are regularly showcased at major events like the RMB Latitudes Art Fair, connecting our artists with a discerning audience of collectors.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Eleven_Editions.jpg?v=1756734056</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 08:50:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_madlozi_contemporary_art_gallery-1</g:id>
      <title>Madlozi Contemporary Art Gallery</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_madlozi_contemporary_art_gallery-1</link>
      <description>Madlozi Contemporary Art Gallery is an international, South African-based gallery dedicated to supporting artists across the African diaspora. Founded by curator, filmmaker, and cultural producer Beathur Mgoza Baker, the Black-owned gallery champions diverse cultural, racial, and gender identities, providing a platform for both emerging and established artists. Through exhibitions and events, Madlozi engages with critical socio-cultural, political, environmental, and humanitarian themes, collaborating with communities, non-profits, and creative partners worldwide. The gallery connects collectors and audiences to exceptional artworks, fostering appreciation, cultural dialogue, and the growth of Africa’s creative economy.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Madlozi_Contemporary_Art_Gallery.png?v=1756735902</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 17:31:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_sibusiso_gcaba-1</g:id>
      <title>Sibusiso Gcaba</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_sibusiso_gcaba-1</link>
      <description>Sibusiso Gcaba (b. 1989, Johannesburg) is a photographer whose work spans multimedia, film, and photography. He studied at Market Photo Workshop, Umuzi, Skyrink Studios, and Through The Lense. Gcaba has exhibited locally and internationally, including the Yaounde Photo Festival (Cameroon), FNB Art Joburg Fair, and European shows in Gothenburg and Munich. He is a 2022 Tierney Fellowship Award recipient and participated in the 2023 New York Times Portfolio Review.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Sibusiso_Gcaba.jpg?v=1756737189</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:27:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_dyman_gallery-1</g:id>
      <title>Dyman Gallery</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_dyman_gallery-1</link>
      <description>Galleries specializing in contemporary art</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:27:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_ooa_gallery_out_of_africa_gallery-1</g:id>
      <title>OOA Gallery (Out of Africa Gallery)</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_ooa_gallery_out_of_africa_gallery-1</link>
      <description>OOA Gallery (Out of Africa Gallery), founded in 2013 in Sitges, Spain, champions contemporary African art and works with artists, collectors, and institutions worldwide. The gallery provides a platform for emerging and established artists to express their narratives and grow their practice. OOA hosts eight annual exhibitions showcasing African artists known for originality and freedom of expression. It has expanded internationally with a London space and, from April, an Olivella, Barcelona residency program offering accommodation, materials, and cultural exchanges to support artistic creation and engagement with collectors and media.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/OOA_Gallery__Out_of_Africa_Gallery.jpg?v=1756736737</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:27:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_dale_sargent_fine_art-1</g:id>
      <title>Dale Sargent Fine Art</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_dale_sargent_fine_art-1</link>
      <description>Established in 2010, Dale Sargent Fine Art is a premier gallery and online platform specializing in fine South African art. For over 15 years, the gallery has offered an extensive collection of works by both established masters and compelling emerging artists. Dale Sargent Fine Art operates a private viewing space in Parktown North, Johannesburg, where visits are available by appointment. This is complemented by a robust online platform, offering collectors access to the collection from anywhere in the world. The gallery also provides a range of specialized services, including expert onsite consulting and personalized art sourcing for both private and corporate clients, assisting them in building and enhancing their collections with significant works.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Dale_Sargent_Fine_Art_thumbnail.png?v=1759315209</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:27:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_david_krut_projects-1</g:id>
      <title>David Krut Projects</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_david_krut_projects-1</link>
      <description>Established in 2002, David Krut Projects(DKP) operates across Johannesburg with spaces at Arts on Main and the Blue House in Parkwood. It encompasses galleries, a bookstore, a publishing arm, framing, and educational facilities. The David Krut Workshop (DKW), founded in 2002 and now based at Arts on Main, collaborates with leading artists such as William Kentridge, Deborah Bell, and Maja Maljević to produce fine art editions and unique works on paper. DKP’s exhibitions showcase these collaborations and support emerging and established artists, while its training program nurtures future arts professionals.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/David_Krut_Projects.jpg?v=1756733520</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:27:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_deepest_darkest-1</g:id>
      <title>Deepest Darkest</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_deepest_darkest-1</link>
      <description>Galleries specializing in contemporary art</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:27:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_ebonycurated</g:id>
      <title>EBONY/CURATED</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_ebonycurated</link>
      <description>Established in 2007, EBONY/CURATED is a leading South African gallery with prominent spaces in Cape Town and Franschhoek. For nearly two decades, the gallery has been dedicated to showcasing contemporary and modern art from the African continent and its wider diaspora. The gallery is renowned for its well-established program, which is committed to both nurturing emerging talent and representing the region&apos;s most significant creative voices. Artists represented by EBONY/CURATED have achieved significant international recognition, with works featured in museum exhibitions and held in major public and private collections worldwide. A regular participant in premier art fairs such as Expo Chicago, 1-54 London, and the Investec Cape Town Art Fair, EBONY/CURATED is a key conduit between the vibrant art scene of Southern Africa and the global art market.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/EBONY_CURATED_thumbnail.png?v=1759394757</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:27:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_first_floor_gallery_harare-1</g:id>
      <title>First Floor Gallery Harare</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_first_floor_gallery_harare-1</link>
      <description>Founded in 2009 as an experimental, artist-run initiative in Harare, First Floor Gallery is Zimbabwe’s leading contemporary art space. The gallery combines commercial practice with artist development, education, and social engagement, and has been instrumental in launching the international careers of numerous Zimbabwean and regional artists. In 2020, it expanded to Victoria Falls, Zimbabwe’s leading international destination, to reach broader audiences and support emerging local talent. With its dual locations and dynamic programming, First Floor Gallery continues to champion contemporary art and nurture the growth of Zimbabwe’s creative community.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/First_Floor_Gallery_Harare.png?v=1756734309</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:27:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_gallery_2</g:id>
      <title>Gallery 2</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_gallery_2</link>
      <description>For over 25 years, Gallery 2 has been a leading fine art gallery in South Africa, dedicated to showcasing contemporary artists and nurturing emerging talent. Founded as Gallery at the Square and rebranded in 2010, it is now based in Johannesburg’s vibrant Parkwood art district. Renowned for its dynamic program and artist support, Gallery 2 also offers expert art consultancy services for private collectors and major corporate projects. It remains a cornerstone of Johannesburg’s art scene, championing the creativity and vision of South Africa’s visual artists.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Gallery_2_thumbnail.jpg?v=1759400836</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:27:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_the_melrose_gallery-1</g:id>
      <title>The Melrose Gallery</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_the_melrose_gallery-1</link>
      <description>The Melrose Gallery – known as &quot;The Gallery of the People&quot; – is a leading Pan-African contemporary art space with locations in Johannesburg and Cape Town. Grounded in African identity, culture, and spirituality, the gallery provides a dynamic platform for artists, collectors, and the public to share stories and creative practices across disciplines, from visual art to dance, poetry, and music. The gallery represents iconic artists such as Dr. Esther Mahlangu, Mam Noria Mabasa, Dr. Willie Bester, and Pitika Ntuli, alongside emerging African talent. Hosting solo and group exhibitions, participating in major art fairs, and collaborating with museums and national galleries, The Melrose Gallery supports artists’ careers while engaging a global audience with vibrant and culturally rooted contemporary art.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/The_Melrose_Gallery.png?v=1756737892</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:27:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_mmarthouse-1</g:id>
      <title>mmARTHouse</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_mmarthouse-1</link>
      <description>Galleries specializing in contemporary art</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:27:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_litty__contemporary-1</g:id>
      <title>LITTY | Contemporary</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_litty__contemporary-1</link>
      <description>Galleries specializing in contemporary art</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:27:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_no_end_contemporary-1</g:id>
      <title>No End Contemporary</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_no_end_contemporary-1</link>
      <description>No End Contemporary Art Space is an artist-run gallery in Linden, Johannesburg, founded in 2015 by Maaike Bakker, Jayne Crawshay-Hall, and Dalene Victor Meyer. The gallery showcases contemporary South African artists across various media, supporting young artists and curators while encouraging both emerging and established collectors to invest in art, fostering a sustainable contemporary art ecosystem.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/No_End_Contemporary.png?v=1756736655</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:27:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_association_for_visual_arts-1</g:id>
      <title>Association for Visual Arts</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_association_for_visual_arts-1</link>
      <description>The Association for Visual Arts (AVA), with roots in the 1850 South African Fine Arts Society, is one of the country’s oldest art institutions. Renamed the Association for Visual Arts in 1995, it continues to foster cultural exchange and arts development, with its legacy tied to the foundation of the South African National Gallery.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Association_for_Visual_Arts.png?v=1756732518</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 07:10:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_the_artists_press-1</g:id>
      <title>The Artists&apos; Press</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_the_artists_press-1</link>
      <description>Since 1991, The Artists’ Press has been a leading South African studio dedicated to creating the finest limited-edition prints in collaboration with artists. Founded by Tamarind Master Printer Mark Attwood, the studio specializes in hand-printed lithographs, combining world-class technical expertise with artistic vision. Our commitment to quality is uncompromising. Each original print is created on acid-free paper with the most light-fast inks available. To preserve the integrity and value of every edition, all works are signed and numbered by the artist, and the printing plate or stone is defaced upon completion. As a fully off-grid, solar-powered studio, we are also dedicated to environmental responsibility, demonstrating that world-class art can be made with a conscience.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/The_Artists__Press.jpg?v=1756737860</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 13:50:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_artist_proof_studio-1</g:id>
      <title>Artist Proof Studio</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_artist_proof_studio-1</link>
      <description>Leaders in fine art printmaking excellence since 1991, Artist Proof Studio (APS) specialise in arts training, print collaborations, partnerships, sales and distribution of prints. APS is a multi-faceted community-centred organisation that trains talented students in South Africa and other countries in Africa. Our graduates are better positioned to become leading art practitioners in the market. Graduate and alumni artists are proudly represented through APS at art fairs, and reputable art galleries throughout the country and internationally. As a centre of printmaking excellence we attract opportunities to collaborate with prominent South African artists who work with our team of experienced printers to create exciting print editions.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Artist_Proof_Studio.png?v=1756732428</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 07:17:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_tumisang_khalipha-1</g:id>
      <title>Tumisang Khalipha</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_tumisang_khalipha-1</link>
      <description>Tumisang Khalipha explores the impact of societal and industrial processes on human existence and the natural world. His work encourages reflection on humanity’s collective responsibility and the search for inner and environmental balance, highlighting the consequences of our actions on life itself.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Tumisang_Khalipha.png?v=1756737951</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:27:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_manzart-1</g:id>
      <title>manZArt</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_manzart-1</link>
      <description>Galleries specializing in contemporary art</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:27:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_smtng_good</g:id>
      <title>SMTNG GOOD</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_smtng_good</link>
      <description>Something Good Studio is a collaborative textile design studio from Johannesburg, founded on the pursuit of a good life. We partner with artists and designers to create stand-out textile pieces that encourage well-being, happiness, and purpose. Our goal is to use art and design to make a gentle, positive impact on the world. Proudly made in South Africa from locally sourced natural fibres, our high-quality textiles are created in limited-edition batches to be enjoyed for a lifetime. Discover our collections online, via select retail stockists, or inquire about our custom design services for special projects.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/SMTNG_GOOD.jpg?v=1756737383</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:27:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_131_a_gallery</g:id>
      <title>131 A Gallery</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/131_a_gallery</link>
      <description>131 A GALLERY is an independent art gallery in Cape Town, dedicated to showcasing the best of contemporary South African art. We champion both renowned and emerging artists, offering a dynamic space for discovery and connection. Visit us at our Sir Lowry Road location, where we host monthly solo and group shows in our main gallery and specially curated exhibitions in our Annex space. Beyond our exhibitions, we offer a suite of personalized services for collectors. We can help you curate the perfect collection for your home or office, arrange intimate studio visits with our extensive network of artists, and manage all local and international shipping logistics to ensure your artwork arrives safely and on time. Whether you are a seasoned collector or just beginning your journey, we invite you to explore the vibrant world of South African contemporary art with us.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/1_22_56bfca11-792c-4fb8-b116-5e82fecb6da9.png?v=1758191173</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 12:14:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_creative_block_by_spier_arts_trust</g:id>
      <title>Creative Block By Spier Arts Trust</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_creative_block_by_spier_arts_trust</link>
      <description>The Creative Block, curated by Tamlin Blake, showcases 260+ South African artists, reflecting diverse stories and contemporary culture. Each artwork reflects a unique story and style, collectively offering a rich expression of contemporary South African culture.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Creative_Block_By_Spier_Arts_Trust.png?v=1756733478</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 08:57:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_lizamore__associates</g:id>
      <title>Lizamore &amp; Associates</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_lizamore__associates</link>
      <description>Founded in 2001, Lizamore &amp; Associates is a leading Johannesburg gallery known for its integrity and commitment to South African contemporary art. The gallery showcases both established and emerging artists, offering collectors a balance of innovation and investment value. With spaces in Parkwood and Rosebank, Lizamore &amp; Associates continues to champion local talent through dynamic exhibitions and participation in major art fairs such as Latitudes, Turbine Art Fair, and CTAF.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Lizamore___Associates.jpg?v=1756735746</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_guns__rain</g:id>
      <title>Guns &amp; Rain</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_guns__rain</link>
      <description>Founded in 2014, Guns &amp; Rain was among the first online platforms for contemporary African art, created to counter the continent’s under-representation in the global digital space. Now based both online and in Johannesburg, the gallery focuses on emerging artists from Southern Africa and beyond who engage with themes of identity, culture, and social change. Named after anthropologist David Lan’s Guns and Rain, the gallery reflects ideas of struggle, land, and transformation, offering a vital platform for the next generation of African voices in contemporary art.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Guns_Rain_thumbnail.png?v=1759401577</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_99_loop_gallery</g:id>
      <title>99 Loop Gallery</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_99_loop_gallery</link>
      <description>99 Loop Gallery is a contemporary art space founded in 2015 and based in Cape Town, South Africa. The gallery operates on the belief that it should be a dynamic space for discovery—one that challenges convention and contributes to the evolving dialogue of contemporary art. It has a particular curatorial focus on painting and prioritises collaboration with both established and emerging local talent. Functioning as an accessible platform, 99 Loop supports creatives whose practices engage with intimate lived experiences situated within larger cultural and aesthetic contexts. Through its rotating exhibition program of solo and group shows, the gallery is a space dedicated to presenting fresh, subversive, and essential voices shaping South African art today.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/99_Loop_Gallery_thumbnail.jpg?v=1758186299</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 08:54:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_latitudes_online</g:id>
      <title>Latitudes Online</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_latitudes_online</link>
      <description>Latitudes Online is a leading platform for discovering and buying contemporary art from Africa and its diaspora. Featuring a curated, ever-changing selection from galleries, curators, studios, and independent artists, it offers an accessible and engaging way to explore the continent’s vibrant creativity.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Latitudes_Online.jpg?v=1756735548</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_doyle_wham</g:id>
      <title>Doyle Wham</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_doyle_wham</link>
      <description>Doyle Wham is the United Kingdom&apos;s first and only gallery dedicated exclusively to contemporary African photography. Founded in 2020, the gallery launched with a nomadic program of exhibitions before establishing its permanent London location in 2022. The gallery is committed to celebrating photography in all its forms and, crucially, to developing the global infrastructure for this field. This is achieved through a dynamic program of exhibitions, international collaborations, and events designed to introduce new artists and build a robust collector base. Doyle Wham’s curatorial program has a particular focus on the intersection of photography with culture, fashion, art, and music, representing a roster of leading artists such as Angèle Etoundi Essamba, Trevor Stuurman, and Yannis Davy Guibinga. As a pioneering platform, Doyle Wham is a vital space for the celebration and promotion of the continent&apos;s most compelling photographic voices.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Doyle_Wham.png?v=1756733912</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_stephen_langa</g:id>
      <title>Stephen Langa</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_stephen_langa</link>
      <description>Stephen Langa (b. 1995, Limpopo) is a Johannesburg-based contemporary artist working in charcoal, watercolor, and oil. Trained at Tshwane North College and Artist Proof Studios, his work explores black experiences, personal journeys, and the intimacy of everyday life. Drawing inspiration from artists like George Pemba, Claude Monet, Gerald Sekoto, and Vincent Van Gogh, Langa’s expressive linework and emotive compositions invite viewers to engage deeply with his subjects and stories.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Stephen_Langa.jpg?v=1756737586</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_akka_project</g:id>
      <title>AKKA Project</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_akka_project</link>
      <description>Galleries specializing in contemporary art</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_alon_skuy</g:id>
      <title>Alon Skuy</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_alon_skuy</link>
      <description>Alon Skuy (b. 1981, Johannesburg) is an award-winning South African photojournalist and chief photographer for the Sunday Times and The Times. A graduate of The Market Photo Workshop, he has covered major national events, including the 2012 Marikana Massacre, earning multiple local and international awards such as POYI’s Photographer of the Year (2020). His long-term projects include documenting xenophobia in South Africa, soon to be published in book form with James Oatway.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/12_copy_1.jpg?v=1762930782</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 06:59:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_tessa_teixeira</g:id>
      <title>Tessa Teixeira</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_tessa_teixeira</link>
      <description>Tessa Teixeira (b. 1969, Ermelo, South Africa) studied Primary Education with a major in Art at the University of the Witwatersrand (1991). In her twenties and thirties, she worked in housing and rural development, founding an NGO that built two schools and later serving with the Mineworkers Development Agency. Since 2006, she has focused on her art practice, pursuing further training in San Francisco and London. Her work explores existential philosophy, ecology, and climate narratives through mixed media, painting, installation, and printmaking. She has exhibited widely in South Africa, the USA, and Europe, including 1.5 Degrees (Berlin, 2021), What’s Next for Earth? (Stanford, 2021), Enviro Art Gallery (Duke University, 2021), Amref Artball (New York, 2019), Optimism (New York, 2018), Art of Lithography (WAM), and her solo exhibition Nothing Stands Still (Johannesburg Holocaust &amp; Genocide Centre, 2018).</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Tessa_Teixeira.jpg?v=1756737754</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_matt_slater</g:id>
      <title>Matt Slater</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_matt_slater</link>
      <description>Matt Slater (b. 1994, East London, Eastern Cape) is a photographer currently based in Cape Town, South Africa. He trained at the Cape Town School of Photography and works deeply with traditional darkroom and analog processes—film, photograms, bleaching, dyes—and experiments with “imperfections” (scratches, corrosion, chemical effects) to merge image and process. Slater’s art often explores themes of impermanence, transience, mortality, and nature. His key projects include The Arboretum (2017) and Efflorescent Cherry (2018), the latter published via Quiet Sun Books. His work has appeared in outlets like Od Review, Musée Magazine, and GUP Magazine.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Matt_Slater.jpg?v=1756736039</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_bonita_alice</g:id>
      <title>Bonita Alice</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_bonita_alice</link>
      <description>Bonita Alice (b. 1962, Johannesburg) is a contemporary South African artist whose practice spans sculpture and mixed media. Her work examines humanity’s fraught relationship with animals and the natural world, exploring how ecological destruction mirrors social injustice and power imbalance. Trained as a sculptor at Wits under Peter Schütz, Alice works primarily in carved wood and in woollen dust on paper—a fragile, tactile medium she developed as an extension of her sculptural practice. Her imagery, influenced by Japanese, Chinese, and Indian aesthetics, often combines beauty and brutality to underscore the tension between violence and delicacy. After 13 years in London, she is now based in Cape Town. Alice has exhibited widely, with work held in major collections including the Johannesburg Art Gallery, Wits Art Museum, and the South African Reserve Bank. She is represented by Everard Read Galleries in London and Cape Town.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Bonita_Alice_db16e77f-fce6-42c5-a0fe-8960ce8838e8.jpg?v=1756732944</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:58:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_jordan_anthony</g:id>
      <title>Jordan Anthony</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_jordan_anthony</link>
      <description>Operating between Cape Town and Durban, Jordan Anthony (b. 1999) is a film photographer, curator, and arts writer who grew up in KwaZulu Natal and graduated from the University of the Witwatersrand, Johannesburg with a Bachelor of Art in Fine Arts. During her studies, she explored subjects in archaeology and psychology, including themes such as healing, dreams, and intuitive creation in her art practice. Anthony has since collaborated with various professionals in the local art industry, including the KZNSA Gallery in Durban (with Strauss &amp; Co.) and Turbine Art Fair (via overheard in the gallery). Her interests also extend into philosophy, memory, and prehistory.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Jordan_Anthony.png?v=1756735131</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_zannele_libambo</g:id>
      <title>Zannele Libambo</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_zannele_libambo</link>
      <description>Zannele Charlotte Libambo (b. 1997, Mpumalanga, South Africa) is a visual arts professional and cultural officer intern. She holds a National Diploma in Fine Arts from Vaal University of Technology and serves on the Visual Arts panel at the National Arts Council. As a curator and mentor, she has led exhibitions including Identify with Me and What Makes Your Heart Fly, exploring themes of identity, life lessons, and artists’ stories.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Zannele_Libambo.png?v=1756738358</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_billy_monk_collection</g:id>
      <title>Billy Monk Collection</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_billy_monk_collection</link>
      <description>The Billy Monk Collection is the official and sole custodian of the photographic archive of Billy Monk. Operating with the full support of the artist&apos;s daughter, Collette Monk, the Collection is dedicated to the preservation and management of this unique body of work. Though physically small, Monk&apos;s archive is a vital and irreplaceable document of life in 1960s Cape Town, offering an unfiltered glimpse into a specific time and place. The primary mission of the Billy Monk Collection is to safeguard this important opus and ensure its legacy is preserved for future generations of researchers, curators, and art lovers. The Collection is managed by Gavin Furlonger and Craig Cameron-Mackintosh.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Billy_Monk_Collection.jpg?v=1756732781</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 06:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_phumulani_ntuli</g:id>
      <title>Phumulani Ntuli</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_phumulani_ntuli</link>
      <description>Phumulani Ntuli holds an MFA in Arts in the Public Sphere from ECAV, Sierre, Switzerland, where he received the Prix-excellence for his research project Permutations of an Event, exploring archives, surveillance, and historical gaps. His multidisciplinary practice spans sculpture, video installations, performance, and artistic research, engaging diverse audiences while interrogating history, memory, and decolonial frameworks. Ntuli has exhibited and performed internationally, including the 2016 Kampala Biennale, Bone Performance Festival (Switzerland), and Act Festival (Geneva, Basel, Sierre, Zurich), and participated in residencies at Fondazione Pistoletto (Italy) and Alps Art Academy (Switzerland).</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Phumulani_Ntuli.jpg?v=1756736816</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_thato_toeba</g:id>
      <title>Thato Toeba</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_thato_toeba</link>
      <description>Thato Toeba is a Lesotho artist and legal scholar currently called flattendacurve (b.1990, Maseru). She shares visuals of continuing thoughts on personhood, politics, propaganda, nationality, globalisation, law and culture. Her work is influenced by her suspicion of formal things (culture law, politics, institutions,) as sober, objective, neutral tools in resolving growing crises of being here in the world today. She speculates on the intrusion of formal things in the emancipated joy of life, womb to tomb and fantasises about some kind of sweet chaos to be master in a less theorised life. She is a LLD candidate at UWC.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Thato_Toeba.jpg?v=1756737809</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 04:23:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_sera_holland</g:id>
      <title>Sera Holland</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_sera_holland</link>
      <description>Sera Holland is a designer and emerging artist based at the foot of Table Mountain, Cape Town. She is known for her thick impasto oil paintings, particularly her playful palette scallops made from leftover paint. Inspired by her natural surroundings, Sera also works with ceramics, creating, painting, and carving on the wheel.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Sera_Holland.jpg?v=1756737177</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 04:25:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_jo_rogge</g:id>
      <title>Jo Rogge</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_jo_rogge</link>
      <description>Jo Rogge is a nonbinary multidisciplinary artist working in painting, printmaking, textiles, and sculpture. Their work explores displacement, family lineage, identity, and challenges heteronormative assumptions around gender and sexuality, using personal symbols and intuitive forms. Rogge also draws on experience in human-rights-focused design, having worked with UNICEF Namibia, ARASA, and WHO Namibia. They have exhibited widely, locally and internationally, and founded NJE Collective, supporting female and marginalized Southern African artists, with a current focus on queer narratives. Rogge lives and works between Namibia and South Africa.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Jo_Rogge_f8918104-f985-4f15-b3d0-bccb3166eda9.jpg?v=1756735135</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_sylvester_falata</g:id>
      <title>Sylvester Falata</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_sylvester_falata</link>
      <description>Sylvester Falata (b. 1985, De-Aar, South Africa) is a Johannesburg-based artist whose practice spans visual art and fashion. He began creating art at Mmabatho High School and later launched his eponymous fashion label in 2010, showcasing at South African Fashion Week and internationally. Falata’s work reflects his fashion background, emphasizing bold color, texture, and experimental proportions.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Sylvester_Falata.jpg?v=1756737673</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_nicola_taylor</g:id>
      <title>Nicola Taylor</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_nicola_taylor</link>
      <description>Nicola Taylor (b.1984) is a visual artist from South Africa. In the context of belonging and connection, Nicola investigates natural laws and matter taking form. Using paint, animation, light installations and sculpture, she explores the human experience from a quantum perspective, looking at unity and identity at a level where manifestation is still physically undecided. Nicola studied in the UK, Italy and South Africa, she has presented five solo exhibitions since 2010, taken part in group shows and collaborations, attended residencies in South Africa and abroad and her work is part of private and public collections.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Nicola_Taylor.jpg?v=1756736581</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_alex_ayivi</g:id>
      <title>Alex Ayivi</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_alex_ayivi</link>
      <description>Alex Ayivi is a French visual artist and printmaker, a graduate of Beaux-Arts de Bourges and ENSAV La Cambre (2018). In 2019, he held Fondation Culture &amp; Diversité’s first residency at Cité Internationale des Arts, presenting his project La MUA. Of Togolese descent, Ayivi explores afrotopia, panafricanism, and family through vibrant works that capture both the exhaustion and serenity of daily life.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Alex_Ayivi_04511298-3daf-4218-8994-5176cedb1862.jpg?v=1756732161</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_lorraine_marcus</g:id>
      <title>Lorraine Marcus</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_lorraine_marcus</link>
      <description>Lorraine Marcus is a South African fine artist with a 30-year career in expressionist painting. Her abstract and figurative work blends emotion, humour, and texture to explore personal experiences, loss, and human expression. Trained under mentors like Lynda Ballen, Phillipa Kotzen, and Gail Mechanic, Marcus works in pastels, oil, and mixed media, creating pieces that convey movement, gesture, and emotional depth. Her art reflects themes of family, maternity, culture, and travel, drawing inspiration from South Africa, Zimbabwe, Europe, Indonesia, and Australia.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Lorraine_Marcus.jpg?v=1756735759</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_lmad_collection_x_latitudes</g:id>
      <title>L&apos;MAD Collection x Latitudes</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_lmad_collection_x_latitudes</link>
      <description>This collection brings together the diverse and powerful voices of: - Cinthia Sifa Mulanga - Shakil Solanki - Io Makandal - Maja Maljević - Jana+Koos - Olivié Keck - Pebofatso Mokoena - Puleng Mongale Shop the collection online at Latitudes or experience the pieces in person at Guillotine Design, 44 Stanley, Johannesburg.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/L_MAD_Collection_x_Latitudes.jpg?v=1756735536</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_phendu_kuta</g:id>
      <title>Phendu Kuta</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_phendu_kuta</link>
      <description>Phendu Kuta is a multidisciplinary creative, curator, and writer, and the founder of Unlabelled Magazine, a platform documenting contemporary African culture and identity through photography. She has contributed to Pan-African publications, academic research, and features such as Rising Stars in VISI, highlighting emerging South African designers and artists. Through Unlabelled, she shares visual stories, collaborates with creative teams and brands, and engages in arts and culture discussions on both local and global platforms.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Phendu_Kuta_thumbnail.png?v=1759327666</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_through_the_lens_collective</g:id>
      <title>Through the Lens Collective</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_through_the_lens_collective</link>
      <description>Through The Lens Collective is a Johannesburg-based organization dedicated to nurturing the next generation of contemporary photographers. Established in 2018 and located at the vibrant Victoria Yards, we provide a crucial space for emerging artists to develop their skills, exhibit their work, and connect with a community of practitioners. Our offerings range from advanced photography courses and portfolio reviews to individual mentorship programs. We are committed to creating platforms for visibility, such as our annual Everyday A Woman social media exhibition, which showcases women photographers across Africa. The Collective has gained international recognition for its work, including a special mention at the Rencontres d&apos;Arles Curatorial Research Grants and being featured in Lenscratch’s prestigious ‘Focus on South Africa’.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Through_the_Lens_Collective.jpg?v=1756737939</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 10:04:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_jillian_ross_print</g:id>
      <title>Jillian Ross Print</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_jillian_ross_print</link>
      <description>Jillian Ross Print is a collaborative printmaking studio dedicated to fostering connections between South African and Canadian artists. Owned and managed by Jillian Ross and Brendan Copestake in Saskatoon, Saskatchewan, the studio is a hub for creating innovative print projects, exhibitions, and educational workshops. With nearly two decades of experience, Jillian Ross Print specializes in collaborative printmaking, contemporary exhibition design, and arts education, partnering with artists, institutions, and galleries to bring unique creative visions to life.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Jillian_Ross_Print.jpg?v=1756735102</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 08:57:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_ilan_godfrey</g:id>
      <title>Ilan Godfrey</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_ilan_godfrey</link>
      <description>Ilan Godfrey is a South African visual artist and photographer whose work documents the social, political, economic, and environmental forces shaping contemporary South Africa. He is best known for Legacy of the Mine (2013), which exposed the human and environmental impact of mining, earning him the Ernest Cole Award, and The Platinum Belt (2016), a multifaceted project on South Africa’s platinum sector. Godfrey’s work has been exhibited globally, including at the National Portrait Gallery (London), Iziko South African National Gallery (Cape Town), Wits Art Museum (Johannesburg), and Musée du quai Branly (Paris), and is held in numerous public and private collections. His photography and writings have appeared in The New Yorker, Le Monde Magazine, ZEIT, Guardian Weekend, and Financial Times Magazine.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Ilan_Godfrey_f3ab682d-da02-4b17-b7e2-22fefb28d6c3.jpg?v=1756734972</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_jessica_michelle_le_roux</g:id>
      <title>Jessica Michelle Le Roux</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_jessica_michelle_le_roux</link>
      <description>Jessica Michelle Le Roux (b.1989, South Africa) is a visual artist working in bronze, ceramics, and digital media. She holds a BA in Sculpture and Printed Image from Tshwane University of Technology (2010). Her work blends 2D and 3D practices, exploring perception, generational thought patterns, and the ripple effects of human action. Known for her use of negative space, grounded figures, and vibrant textures, her art is held in local and international collections. She has exhibited at Investec Cape Town Art Fair, and been featured in Sasol New Signatures, Thami Mnyele, and Absa Ateliers Art Awards. Currently, she is developing her bronze series Senses and collaborating on Revolve: Redition Four.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Jessica_Michelle_Le_Roux.png?v=1756735097</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_mwimbi_fine_art_gallery</g:id>
      <title>Mwimbi Fine Art Gallery</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_mwimbi_fine_art_gallery</link>
      <description>Galleries specializing in contemporary art</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_nomvula_millicent_hoko</g:id>
      <title>Nomvula Millicent Hoko</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_nomvula_millicent_hoko</link>
      <description>Nomvula Millicent Hoko (b. 1996, Soweto, South Africa) is a contemporary visual artist working in painting, printmaking, and mixed media. Her practice explores identity, culture, and ancestral knowledge, creating ethereal, surreal works that bridge tradition and personal narrative. Nomvula is a member of Printing Girls and is currently studying Fine Arts at Walter Sisulu University.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Nomvula_Millicent_Hoko.jpg?v=1756736590</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_keiskamma_art_project</g:id>
      <title>Keiskamma Art Project</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_keiskamma_art_project</link>
      <description>Founded in 2000 in Hamburg, Eastern Cape, the Keiskamma Art Project preserves local memory and oral history through large-scale embroidered artworks. The collective has received numerous accolades, including the BASA Award and the Chairman’s Premier Award (2011) for its extraordinary commitment to the arts. Marking its twentieth anniversary, the retrospective Umaf’ evuka, nje ngenyanga / Dying and Rising as the Moon Does at Constitution Hill, Johannesburg, brings together iconic works exploring themes of community, resilience, and healing. In honour of South Africa’s constitutional values — Equality, Freedom, and Human Dignity — the artists have created three limited-edition tapestries reflecting their hopes and lived experiences. Richly detailed and deeply symbolic, the works embody the power of collective creativity to heal and inspire.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Keiskamma_Art_Project_fb9fa090-6522-4d78-bcc8-da6082503d1e.jpg?v=1756735316</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 14:36:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_tshepiso_moropa</g:id>
      <title>Tshepiso Moropa</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_tshepiso_moropa</link>
      <description>Tshepiso Moropa is a Johannesburg-based visual artist working in photography, collage, and film. Her practice explores identity and storytelling, often using Baroque-inspired techniques that combine dramatic compositions, bold ornamentation, and archival imagery to evoke emotion and tension. Moropa has exhibited internationally, including at Oakstop Gallery in Oakland, USA, and has been featured in publications such as 1854. Photography and The Mail &amp; Guardian.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Tshepiso_Moropa.jpg?v=1756737947</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_onkarabile_nawane</g:id>
      <title>Onkarabile Nawane</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_onkarabile_nawane</link>
      <description>Onkarabile Nawane (b. 1999, Mokgola, Zeerust) is a 24-year-old South African photographer specializing in conceptual, street, and landscape photography. Driven by a passion for storytelling, he uses his camera to capture personal and social narratives, translating memories, experiences, and emotions into visual stories. Nawane’s work transforms everyday moments into poetic, thought-provoking images that connect deeply with viewers and inspire future generations.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Onkarabile_Nawane.jpg?v=1756736697</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_sol_t</g:id>
      <title>Sol T</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_sol_t</link>
      <description>Soliana (Sol) is a first-generation Eritrean-South African storyteller. Drawing from diverse life experiences, she explores the universal desire for peace, love, and being heard. With a background as a producer and scriptwriter in South African film and television, Soliana aims to create Pan-African co-productions, sharing Africa’s rich stories with the world and highlighting the continent’s creativity and resilience.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Sol_T.jpg?v=1756737389</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_lerato_nkosi</g:id>
      <title>Lerato Nkosi</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_lerato_nkosi</link>
      <description>Lerato Nkosi (b. 1993, Mpumalanga) is a Johannesburg-based artist whose work explores womanhood, identity, and inherited teachings. Using ink and stamps as metaphors for authority and permanence, she examines how societal expectations shape the female experience. Nkosi is the winner of the inaugural ANNA Award and has exhibited widely, including at the Turbine Art Fair and Pretoria Art Museum.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Lerato_Nkosi.jpg?v=1756735739</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_gugulethu_mnguni</g:id>
      <title>Gugulethu Mnguni</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_gugulethu_mnguni</link>
      <description>Gugulethu Mnguni (b. Soweto, South Africa) is a Johannesburg-based visual artist specializing in watercolour, monotype, and linocut. She graduated from Artist Proof Studio in 2021 and is currently completing a senior program to further develop her practice. Mnguni has participated in projects such as Art in Action (2021), the ILRIG project (2022), a climate change initiative (2020), and recently exhibited at the Cape Town Art Fair.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Gugulethu_Mnguni.png?v=1756734709</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 04:23:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_hemali_khoosal</g:id>
      <title>Hemali Khoosal</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_hemali_khoosal</link>
      <description>Hemali Khoosal is a socially engaged, multidisciplinary artist and researcher based in Johannesburg. A Fine Arts graduate from Wits School of Art, she also holds a Master’s in Cinematography from Goldsmiths, University of London. Khoosal’s work explores human perception, gesture, language, migration, and intergenerational knowledge through collaborative video, installation, and performance. Her practice has earned numerous awards, including a Commonwealth Scholarship, the Sam Nhlengethwa Young Womxn Award, and the Giovanna Milner Award. She has held residencies at The Spinnerei, Leipzig, and the Bag Factory, and her work is included in collections such as the Centro Luigi di Sarro and the Jack Ginsberg Collection.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Hemali_Khoosal_baa60b90-5f77-442c-a72e-c02c104d624c.jpg?v=1756734961</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 04:25:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_farhana_jacobs</g:id>
      <title>Farhana Jacobs</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_farhana_jacobs</link>
      <description>Farhana Jacobs is a self-taught Johannesburg-based artist, born in Durban and trained in Social Anthropology at the University of Cape Town. Her work explores women’s relationships with their bodies, surroundings, and the structures of patriarchy, presenting the female form as a landscape of contestation and imagination. Jacobs’ practice interrogates autonomy, narratives, and the unseen effects of societal systems. She has exhibited at Turbine Art Fair, Bubblegum Gallery, and AfricaNXT, and her work has been featured in publications including Creative Knowledge Resources and African Writer Magazine.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Farhana_Jacobs.png?v=1756734156</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_fiona_davhana</g:id>
      <title>Fiona Davhana</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_fiona_davhana</link>
      <description>(Dembe) Fiona Davhana (b.1996, Thohoyandou, Limpopo) is a multidisciplinary artist based in Johannesburg. She works across painting, doodling, photography, and writing, and is currently pursuing an Advanced Photography course at the Market Photo Workshop. Her work has been featured in publications including Afro-Punk (2016), Odd Magazine (2020), and Heavy Iridescent (2020). She has exhibited with the Through the Lens Collective in shows such as The Portrait Show (2020) and Everyday a Woman (2020), and will participate in Postcard Africa later in 2025. Davhana has completed workshops at MoMA, NEMISA, and Benrose Studios, and was recognized as a Design Indaba Emerging Creative in 2021. She has also facilitated talks, including the Last Thursday Talk for the Dior Photography and Visual Arts Award for Young Talents (2022).</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Fiona_Davhana.png?v=1756734291</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_sinalo_ngcaba</g:id>
      <title>Sinalo Ngcaba</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_sinalo_ngcaba</link>
      <description>Sinalo Ngcaba (b. 1996) is a Johannesburg-based visual artist from East London and Bizana. Self-taught in technique, she studied design in advertising at Umuzi Academy, where she learned about the creative industry. Working across oil pastels, ink, digital, and paint, Ngcaba explores black joy, pop culture, womanhood, and human rights, using art as a tool to tell stories and evoke change. She has collaborated with brands and creatives including Nike, Aperol Spritz, Comedy Central Africa, NATIVE Mag, and Piano People UK.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Sinalo_Ngcaba.png?v=1756737368</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 04:23:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_everard_read_gallery_cape_town</g:id>
      <title>Everard Read Gallery Cape Town</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_everard_read_gallery_cape_town</link>
      <description>Founded in 1913, Everard Read is Africa&apos;s oldest and largest commercial art gallery. For over a century, it has been a premier institution in the South African art world, dedicated to showcasing the country&apos;s finest contemporary artists. With seven distinct galleries across four key locations—Johannesburg, Cape Town, London, and Franschhoek—Everard Read offers an international platform for artists from diverse backgrounds. The gallery&apos;s mission is to support artists who are committed to contemporary storytelling, exceptional craft, and the making of meaning. It champions work that interrogates both universal and Afrocentric ideas, creating contemporary icons that inspire contemplation, introspection, and awe. Everard Read is committed to the long-term representation of exceptional, established voices while continuously seeking out and nurturing the next generation of talent, ensuring a dynamic and relevant program.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/everard-read-headshot-thumbnail.png?v=1759396481</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_philippa_allen</g:id>
      <title>Philippa Allen</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_philippa_allen</link>
      <description>Philippa Allen (b. 1969, South Africa) is a Cape Town–based artist whose work draws inspiration from local landscapes. Using charcoal, panpastel, and acrylic layering, she explores the beauty, fragility, and persistence of nature, often manipulating surfaces to challenge viewers’ perceptions. Allen has exhibited extensively since 2003, with recent solo shows including Evoking Place (Sisonke Gallery, 2023) and Ghostscapes (AVA Gallery, 2020). Her work reflects on the intersections of environment, mental health, and human wellbeing.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Philippa_Allen.jpg?v=1756736804</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_kayleigh_fisher</g:id>
      <title>Kay-Leigh Fisher</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_kayleigh_fisher</link>
      <description>Kay-Leigh Fisher is a Johannesburg-based visual artist, curator, and publisher whose work explores identity, race, gender, and the process of unlearning in counter-cultural spaces. Her practice often extends into publishing as a form of curatorial intervention. Fisher holds a BA in Fine Arts from Wits University (2019) and an Honours in Curatorship from the Michaelis School of Fine Art (2020).</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Kay-Leigh_Fisher_6e79078a-c1f7-48f4-acb4-9a7d393ed3e4.jpg?v=1756735205</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_cameron_platter</g:id>
      <title>Cameron Platter</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_cameron_platter</link>
      <description>Cameron Platter is a South African artist whose vivid mixed-media works explore excess and consumption. Working across drawing, sculpture, painting, and video, Platter addresses themes of sex, beauty, politics, and violence with a provocative yet relatable approach. His work is included in the permanent collections of MoMA New York, Zeitz MOCAA, The Frac des Pays de la Loire, The Margulies Collection, and the Iziko South African National Gallery.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Cameron_Platter.png?v=1756733026</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 04:23:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_ros_koch</g:id>
      <title>Ros Koch</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_ros_koch</link>
      <description>Ros Koch (b. 1975, UK) is a South Africa-based artist whose work explores home, identity, and belonging. An immigrant, adventurer, and mother of three, her experiences inform her diverse artistic practice, which spans realism to impressionism. Ros has held multiple solo and group exhibitions, and her work is included in corporate and private collections worldwide. She lives and works in Stellenbosch.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Ros_Koch.png?v=1756736972</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_mulanga_mbedzi</g:id>
      <title>Mulanga Mbedzi</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_mulanga_mbedzi</link>
      <description>Mulanga Mbedzi is a self-taught visual artist whose charcoal drawings explore healing, self-awareness, and identity. Centering the human figure, her work examines how emotional trauma shapes our self-perception and experience of the world, inviting viewers into a dialogue of honest introspection and personal truth. Holding an LLB from the University of the Witwatersrand and an Honours in Political and International Relations from Rhodes University, Mulanga’s academic background deepened her understanding of social issues. Her practice reflects a commitment to addressing their roots—captured in her guiding belief that “hurt people hurt people.”</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Mulanga_Mbedzi.jpg?v=1756736331</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_lusanda_ndita</g:id>
      <title>Lusanda Ndita</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_lusanda_ndita</link>
      <description>Lusanda Ndita is a South African visual artist. In 2017 Ndita completed the Advanced Programme in Photography course at the Market Photo Workshop in Johannesburg. In 2020 he was awarded the Tierney Fellowship. His practice is one of self-investigation, experienced through the guise of cultivating his family&apos;s domestic archive of images, oral narratives and the inclusion of various artefacts, such as an Apartheid dompass book which belonged to his grandfather. His practice serves as a contemporary album which tells the story of his own heritage and life experiences</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Lusanda_Ndita.jpg?v=1756735868</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_khanya_zibaya</g:id>
      <title>Khanya ZIbaya</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_khanya_zibaya</link>
      <description>Khanya Zibaya grew up a curious child, always inquisitive about his surroundings. This led to an early realisation of what he calls, “the chase of life” - that is, the multilayered and complex faces people wear in society. Zibaya’s passion for telling stories stemmed from unravelling these layers. As an alumni of the Market Theatre Laboratory, he creates photographs with his cellphone.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Khanya_ZIbaya_92e73693-7cf7-42b3-b504-e1497198f9af.jpg?v=1756735354</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 04:23:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_leanie_barnard</g:id>
      <title>Leanie Barnard</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_leanie_barnard</link>
      <description>Leanie Barnard Mentz, born in Pretoria and a graduate of the Open Window Art Academy (2004), is a multidisciplinary artist and floral designer known for her expressive large-scale paintings and drawings. Working with thick layers of paint and charcoal, she explores the fluid boundaries between reality and perception, revealing traces of the human condition through gesture, imperfection, and movement. Her work embraces ambiguity and emotion, reflecting on what we choose to reveal or conceal in a world obsessed with perfection.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Leanie_Barnard.jpg?v=1756735566</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_jono_dry</g:id>
      <title>Jono Dry</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_jono_dry</link>
      <description>Jono Dry is a self-taught South African artist specializing in large-scale hyperrealist graphite drawings. Each work can take up to two months and 200 hours to complete, reflecting his meticulous approach and devotion to perfection. He produces limited edition Giclée prints from his originals. Exhibiting locally and internationally, Dry pushes the boundaries of graphite, using rich visuals and storytelling to emphasize the passage of time and the emotional power of his work.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Jono_Dry_8c5bfe66-4b1c-402a-b6a9-41dba3b2dc3b.jpg?v=1756735109</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_kirti_ranchod</g:id>
      <title>Kirti Ranchod</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_kirti_ranchod</link>
      <description>Kirti Ranchod is a neurologist and brain health consultant based in Johannesburg, South Africa, with a special interest in neuroaesthetics and the impact of art on brain health. Her creative journey began at age eight, guided by her father, and has remained intertwined with her medical practice. Drawing on her cultural background and professional experience, Kirti’s art explores the intersections of neuroscience, creativity, and yogic science—examining how visual language and symbols influence perception, and in turn, shape reality.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Kirti_Ranchod.jpg?v=1756735396</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_origin_art</g:id>
      <title>Origin Art</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_origin_art</link>
      <description>Origin Art is dedicated to pushing boundaries and reflecting on global diversity and inclusion through art. The gallery builds a sustainable community of artists and audiences, fostering experimentation and collaboration across South Africa and internationally. By supporting artists as they grow and gain recognition, Origin Art aims to evolve alongside them, engaging across disciplines and partnerships to explore new frontiers in the art world.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Origin_Art.jpg?v=1756736741</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 07:25:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_christopher_moller_gallery</g:id>
      <title>Christopher Moller Gallery</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_christopher_moller_gallery</link>
      <description>Christopher Moller Gallery is one of South Africa&apos;s leading contemporary art galleries, founded on a passion for empowering artists and fostering meaningful artistic dialogue. Situated in a charming Victorian home in Cape Town, the gallery offers a unique environment where traditional and modern aesthetics converge. This intimate setting provides a nurturing space for artists to grow and for collectors to discover works of exceptional quality. As dedicated collectors themselves, the gallery&apos;s team is committed to showcasing artists whose work is relevant, thought-provoking, and impactful. They provide a highly personalized art buying experience, guided by integrity, artistic vision, and a deep appreciation for excellence. With an ever-evolving program of exhibitions available both in-person and virtually, Christopher Moller Gallery invites you to explore the power of contemporary art.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Christopher_Moller_Gallery.png?v=1756733382</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:28:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_bria_fernandes</g:id>
      <title>Bria Fernandes</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_bria_fernandes</link>
      <description>Bria Fernandes is a Canadian figurative painter whose work delves into the quiet, often overlooked, spaces of the human psyche. Through her evocative portraits, she explores profound themes of introspection, silence, and the vastness of the unspoken. Her subjects are frequently depicted in moments of passive contemplation or deep reflection, their stillness acting as a powerful gateway for the viewer. By capturing these states of being, Fernandes masterfully examines the delicate nature of vulnerability, the subtle weight of oppression, and the hidden currents of consciousness that lie just beneath the surface. Born in Ottawa, Ontario, and now based in Winnipeg, Manitoba, Fernandes&apos;s artistic practice is shaped by a dedicated academic journey. She began her formal training at the University of Manitoba’s School of Fine Art, where she laid the groundwork for her thematic explorations. Currently, she is completing her Bachelor of Fine Arts at the Alberta University of the Arts, further refining her distinctive voice and the conceptual depth of her compelling work.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Bria_Fernandes.jpg?v=1756732984</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_chelsea_selvan</g:id>
      <title>Chelsea Selvan</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_chelsea_selvan</link>
      <description>Chelsea Selvan (b. 1997, Johannesburg) is a South African artist and writer with a BA Fine Arts (distinction) from Wits. Her printmaking explores memory through fluid colour fields, calligraphic marks, and geometric forms that echo fleeting thoughts and architectural spaces. She was awarded the 2022 ABSA L’Atelier Award and presented her debut solo exhibition at Gallery 2 in 2024.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Chelsea_Selvan.png?v=1756733196</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_nano_le_face</g:id>
      <title>Nano Le Face</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_nano_le_face</link>
      <description>Ntwanano Shilubana (b. 1999) better known as Nano, or simply Le Face is a self-taught visual artist based in Pretoria. He studied Film Arts at Open Window and at AFDA. His work borrows freely from popular culture, and uses humour to mock, critique and parody our obsessions with love, consumerism, fame &amp; ourselves.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Nano_Le_Face.jpg?v=1756736404</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_eugenie_marais</g:id>
      <title>Eugenie Marais</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_eugenie_marais</link>
      <description>Eugenie Marais is a South African visual artist whose paintings depict everyday scenes—bridges, roads, and landscapes—imbued with nostalgia, serenity, and loneliness. Working in oil, acrylic, collage, drawing, printmaking, and mixed media, she often creates series that explore ideas, experiences, and emotions. Marais has held six solo exhibitions, participated in numerous group shows, and collaborated with The Artists’ Press on lithographs and mono prints. Her work is held in private and public collections.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Eugenie_Marais_03bab607-88b0-49a4-b8a4-f32bb2b1a830.jpg?v=1756734062</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_dela_anyah</g:id>
      <title>Dela Anyah</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_dela_anyah</link>
      <description>Dela Anyah is a Ghanaian artist working across sculpture, painting, and installation. Using discarded materials such as inner tubes, tires, and license plates, he explores themes of decay, renewal, and transformation. Influenced by nature and fashion, Anyah weaves rubber into garments and assemblages that reimagine histories and speculative futures of neglected objects. His work is held in collections including the Celine Art Project, Sir David Adjaye, and the Institute Museum of Ghana. Recent exhibitions include Nubuke Foundation, Accra (2023), The Noldor Residency, Accra (2022), and group shows in Tokyo, New York, and Copenhagen.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Dela_Anyah_662cf7c3-113b-4b13-a2c8-0addbdfcbc25.png?v=1756733742</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 04:24:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_justin_southey</g:id>
      <title>Justin Southey</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_justin_southey</link>
      <description>Justin Southey is a South African contemporary artist born in 1985, currently based in Cape Town. He graduated cum laude from the Stellenbosch Academy of Graphic Design and Photography in 2007 with a BA in Applied Design, majoring in photography. Southey&apos;s artistic practice is characterized by large-scale abstract paintings that delve into themes of nature, spirituality, and the unseen emotional and spiritual landscapes. His works often feature bold swathes of color, texture, and exuberant mark-making, creating a dynamic interplay that invites viewers to explore and interpret the underlying narratives.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Justin_Southey_d4c6091f-0ec0-4bb0-bf6f-f2db9d07e4ea.jpg?v=1756735156</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_sunali_narshai</g:id>
      <title>Sunali Narshai</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_sunali_narshai</link>
      <description>Sunali Narshai is a South African visual artist based in Montreal. Working primarily on paper, she combines drawing, painting, and collage to create bold, graphic compositions that explore diasporic identity, selfhood, and emotional aesthetics. Her work spans modern abstraction and figuration, seeking harmony through color and form. Narshai holds a BA in Fine Art from Rhodes University, and her work has been exhibited in South Africa, Helsinki, and at the New York Lift-Off Film Festival.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Sunali_Narshai.jpg?v=1756737665</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_buqaqawuli_nobakada</g:id>
      <title>Buqaqawuli Nobakada</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_buqaqawuli_nobakada</link>
      <description>Buqaqawuli Nobakada (b. 2000, Western Cape, South Africa) is an emerging contemporary mixed-media artist raised between Philippi and Lady Frere, Eastern Cape. Working primarily with acrylic on laced paper, often incorporating custom clay or gold jewellery, her practice explores border crossings—both imagined and real. Nobakada is in her third year of Fine Arts at the University of the Witwatersrand and has exhibited in group shows including I Am &amp; Nothing Else (Affinity Art Gallery, Lagos), Everything Was Beautiful and Nothing Hurt (FNB Art Joburg), and the SOMA exhibition in France.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Buqaqawuli_Nobakada_0a375498-7f60-44f5-9a30-5518acce9424.jpg?v=1756733012</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_akshar_maganbeharie</g:id>
      <title>Akshar Maganbeharie</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_akshar_maganbeharie</link>
      <description>Akshar Maganbeharie (b. 2017, Fine Art, University of the Witwatersrand) is a Cape Town–based multidisciplinary artist working across painting, drawing, and installation. His semi-abstract, impressionistic style reflects pop culture influences—Britney Spears, Starbucks, Kylie Jenner—while engaging themes of identity, cultural imperialism, and capitalism. A member of the Kutti Collective, he has exhibited in Autumn Salon (Gallery Fanon, Johannesburg, 2021), Kutti Bazaar (A4 Arts Foundation, Cape Town, 2021), and Apartment Vol. 2 (The Fourth, Cape Town, 2020).</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Akshar_Maganbeharie_0df36e1a-eef0-4243-b84f-efa3d986f640.jpg?v=1756732126</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_fede_arthouse</g:id>
      <title>FEDE Arthouse</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_fede_arthouse</link>
      <description>Founded in 2020 by artist and curator Lebo Kekana, FEDE Arthouse is a nomadic gallery operating at the intersection of art, design, and culture. Through research-driven and site-specific projects, FEDE explores ‘space-making’ to create alternative, community-oriented exhibition experiences. Collaborating with platforms such as blank projects, Under Projects, and RESERVOIR, FEDE has presented exhibitions across Cape Town and internationally in Ibiza and Barcelona. Rejecting the traditional white-wall format, FEDE embraces a more experimental and culturally engaged approach, using exhibitions as a means to research, connect, and reimagine shared public spaces.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/FEDE_Arthouse.jpg?v=1756734251</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_samkelo_matomela</g:id>
      <title>Samkelo Matomela</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_samkelo_matomela</link>
      <description>Samkelo Matomela (b. 1996, KwaZulu-Natal) is a Johannesburg-based artist trained at Artist Proof Studio in printmaking. Working primarily in painting and drawing, his portraits and figures explore vulnerability, emotion, and the experiences of young men navigating life. Using impasto and symbolic motifs like the butterfly, his work reflects themes of hope, change, and self-reflection, inviting viewers to engage imaginatively with his intimate compositions.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Samkelo_Matomela.jpg?v=1756737063</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_khwezi_strydom</g:id>
      <title>Khwezi Strydom</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_khwezi_strydom</link>
      <description>Khwezi Strydom, born in New Mexico to a South African father and French mother from Tunis, is a painter whose work reflects his fascination with cultural hybridity and identity. Initially drawn to graffiti, skate, and hip-hop culture, he developed a strong foundation in large-scale improvisation and letterforms. After studying astrophysics and training as a glassblower at Cristallerie Saint Louis for five years, he returned to painting full-time in 2012. Strydom currently lives and works in Drôme, France.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Khwezi_Strydom.jpg?v=1756735375</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_motheo_mamabolo</g:id>
      <title>Motheo Mamabolo</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_motheo_mamabolo</link>
      <description>Motheo Mamabolo is a South African interdisciplinary artist and curator whose practice explores the integration of the human psyche within the digital age. Working across culinary art, sound, and visual media, she investigates human existence alongside technological evolution. Her interests focus on food inequality in South Africa, systemic disparities amplified by private institutions in the 4IR era, and speculative art examining Africa’s role in spirituality and mental health practices.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Motheo_Mamabolo.jpg?v=1756736227</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_denzo_nyathi</g:id>
      <title>Denzo Nyathi</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_denzo_nyathi</link>
      <description>Denzel ‘Denzo’ Nyathi is a South African designer, writer, curator, and creative. With a background in Communication Design from Rhodes University, he combines journalism and design to create work that speaks to society. Formerly an art journalist for publications like Bubblegum Club and Mail &amp; Guardian, his curatorial approach explores connections between image, text, and space. His multidisciplinary practice spans visual arts, dance, writing, and design, reflecting a deep interest in how art illuminates human experience.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Denzo_Nyathi.jpg?v=1756733807</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_gemma_hart</g:id>
      <title>Gemma Hart</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_gemma_hart</link>
      <description>Gemma Hart is a Johannesburg-based curator, writer, and facilitator. She holds a BA Fine Arts (2016) and an MA in Contemporary Curatorial Practice (2020), both with distinction, from Wits University. Her research and practice explore the museum as a pedagogical platform, focusing on immersive exhibition-making, the ideology of display, and the lingering power dynamics of colonial legacies in contemporary museums.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Gemma_Hart.jpg?v=1756734516</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_basadi_dibeela</g:id>
      <title>Basadi Dibeela</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_basadi_dibeela</link>
      <description>Basadi Dibeela (She/Her) is a curator, DJ, and freelance arts journalist whose work bridges arts, innovation, and sustainability. Rooted in both village and city contexts, she explores critical cultural placemaking beyond metropolitan centers, questioning the roles of artist, curator, and community in shaping new cultural vocabularies. She is the founder of the Loselo Kultur Network in Kanye, Botswana, and has served on the board of the Kgosi Bathoen II Museum. Basadi holds an MA in Arts Journalism from Syracuse University and a BA in Political Science from the University of Botswana.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Basadi_Dibeela.jpg?v=1756732656</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_carina_ubisse_capitine</g:id>
      <title>Carina Ubisse Capitine</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_carina_ubisse_capitine</link>
      <description>Carina Ubisse Capitine is a Mozambican artivist and communications professional who uses art to amplify marginalized voices and drive social change. Her work explores self-reflection, pleasure, and identity in resistance to the invisibilization and objectification of women. As a curator, she focuses on creating access for underrepresented artists and promoting Afro-centric aesthetics. A Fulbright Scholar, she holds a Master’s in Communication and Development Studies from Ohio University and a Licenciatura in Communication Sciences from Universidade Politécnica in Mozambique.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Carina_Ubisse_Capitine_3c0d1f61-d1c1-4415-bb3c-9477c21a6714.jpg?v=1756733143</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_jadesola_olaniyan</g:id>
      <title>Jadesola Olaniyan</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_jadesola_olaniyan</link>
      <description>Jadesola Olaniyan (b. 1997) is a Lagos-based visual artist, independent curator, and anthropologist. A graduate of the University of British Columbia, her work spans collections-based research and exhibitions with institutions such as the Museum of Anthropology and SMO Contemporary Art. Guided by theories of memory and consciousness, Olaniyan explores how art extends beyond gallery spaces, using collaborative approaches to address challenges faced by artists and communities.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Jadesola_Olaniyan.jpg?v=1756735067</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_kezia_owusuankomah</g:id>
      <title>Kezia Owusu-Ankomah</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_kezia_owusuankomah</link>
      <description>Kezia Ouomoye Owusu-Ankomah is a Ph.D. candidate in Painting and Sculpture, and an art practitioner, curator, writer, and mentor based in Accra, Ghana. She manages ADA Contemporary Art Gallery and has curated numerous exhibitions, including Monologue of Voices and Hulu Shinyoo. She also serves as Operations Advisor at The African Art Hub UK, contributing to the development of African contemporary art locally and internationally.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Kezia_Owusu-Ankomah.jpg?v=1756735351</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_jason_langa</g:id>
      <title>Jason Langa</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_jason_langa</link>
      <description>Jason Langa (b.1997, Johannesburg) is a South African figurative painter and printmaker. Using oil paint and print techniques, he explores nostalgia, identity, memory, and self-discovery. Influenced by Impressionism, his work features expressive brushwork, ethereal blue skin tones, clouds, and closed eyes, evoking introspection and blurring the boundaries between past and present.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Jason_Langa_2c92782d-3d37-4f6b-813b-b4b71141761d.jpg?v=1756735079</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_motlhoki_nono</g:id>
      <title>Motlhoki Nono</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_motlhoki_nono</link>
      <description>Motlhoki Nono (b. 1998, Mabopane, Pretoria) is a Johannesburg-based artist whose work explores the intimate and violent politics of romantic love. Working across video, photography, and printmaking, she investigates how love manifests at the intersection of race, class, and gender. Her practice reflects a decolonial and sociological enquiry into black love—its complexities, domestic spaces, and emotional landscapes. Nono completed her Honours in Fine Art at the University of the Witwatersrand, graduating with five distinctions and two awards.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Motlhoki_Nono.png?v=1756736254</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_hlobile_dube</g:id>
      <title>Hlobile Dube</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_hlobile_dube</link>
      <description>Hlobile Maphumulo (b. 1996, eNanda, South Africa) is a visual artist based in Durban. She studied Art and Design (N4–N6) and gained experience at various art centers and the BAT Center. In 2022, Hlobile transitioned to painting, blending her graphic design background with vibrant, expressive colors. Her work is not focused on realism but on conveying emotion, spirituality, and healing through color, exploring the energy and meaning each hue can hold.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Hlobile_Dube_9a01f4e4-c7b8-405b-9264-493ad4a893ea.jpg?v=1756734969</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_xhanti_zwelendaba</g:id>
      <title>Xhanti Zwelendaba</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_xhanti_zwelendaba</link>
      <description>Xhanti Zwelendaba is a multidisciplinary artist working across sculpture, printmaking, installation, performance, and video. His practice explores the tensions between Xhosa traditions, capitalism, and nationalism, while confronting the lasting effects of colonialism and apartheid. He has exhibited widely, including at the Investec Cape Town Art Fair, FNB Art Joburg, and Turbine Art Fair (Artist of the Year, 2021), and recently completed a residency at the Leipzig International Art Programme in Germany.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Xhanti_Zwelendaba.jpg?v=1756738204</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 04:23:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_warren_maroon</g:id>
      <title>Warren_Maroon</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_warren_maroon</link>
      <description>Warren Maroon (b. 1985) is a Cape Town-based artist and sculptor. Growing up in Mitchell’s Plain on the Cape Flats, Maroon turned to art as a means of escape and expression. Drawing inspiration from an Arte Povera aesthetic, he uses found objects to create sculptural works that reflect on identity, inequality, and lived experiences as a person of colour in South Africa.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Warren_Maroon.jpg?v=1756738069</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 04:23:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_gaelen_pinnock</g:id>
      <title>Gaelen Pinnock</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_gaelen_pinnock</link>
      <description>Gaelen Pinnock (b.1980, South Africa) is a Cape Town-based artist whose work explores power, domesticity, and division within urban landscapes. Originally trained as an architect, Pinnock examines how modern developments and apartheid legacies shape social and spatial inequalities. Using found objects and materials—like security equipment and construction remnants—his work distills patterns of exclusion and tension into stark, conceptual pieces. He has exhibited locally and internationally, including at Zeitz MOCAA, A4 Arts Foundation, and the Rupert Museum.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Gaelen_Pinnock_740f872c-9114-4731-b8ff-9722d6afd1a9.jpg?v=1756734429</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 04:23:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_lebogang_mogul_mabusela</g:id>
      <title>Lebogang Mogul Mabusela</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_lebogang_mogul_mabusela</link>
      <description>Lebogang Mogul Mabusela, born in Mabopane, is a self-proclaimed Zinequeen and Monotypebabe whose practice explores the male form. A Wits Fine Arts graduate (2019) and recipient of the Standard Bank Fine Arts Prize, Mabusela has exhibited widely across South Africa and internationally, including at Frieze London and Lagos. Her debut solo exhibition, Ukwatile? (2022) at Stevenson Gallery, examined language, catcalling, and voyeurism. She currently runs The Monotypebabe Curatorial, a printmaking initiative supporting emerging artists.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Lebogang_Mogul_Mabusela.jpg?v=1756735587</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_maja_maljevi</g:id>
      <title>Maja Maljević</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_maja_maljevi</link>
      <description>Maja Maljević (b. 1973, Belgrade, Serbia) is a Johannesburg-based artist who moved to South Africa in 2000. She holds an MFA from the University of Belgrade (1999). Her work is rooted in gestural abstraction, starting by “dirtying” the canvas with bright layers of paint and building complex surfaces of drips, blocks, and waves of color. Maljević emphasizes physical movement in her process, creating dynamic compositions that balance conflict and harmony. Working across painting, printmaking, and sculpture, she reinterprets Modernist techniques to suit contemporary needs, aiming for coherence and interplay between all elements in her work.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Maja_Maljevic.jpg?v=1756735927</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_alexandra_naledi_holtman</g:id>
      <title>Alexandra Naledi Holtman</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_alexandra_naledi_holtman</link>
      <description>Alexandra Naledi Holtman is a Cape Town-based interdisciplinary artist and graduate of the Michaelis School of Fine Art (UCT). Working across sound, sculpture, and interactive installation, her practice explores communication, connection, and perception. Through playful yet conceptually grounded works—such as her interactive sound installation inspired by Roy Ascott’s theory of telematics—Holtman reimagines digital communication through tactile, lo-fi materials. By translating high-tech ideas into intimate, physical encounters, she invites audiences to reflect on the essence of human connection in an increasingly digital world.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Alexandra_Naledi_Holtman_df27f420-9140-4f19-a468-cf57c5ee36ca.jpg?v=1756732153</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 06:55:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_cazlynne_peffer</g:id>
      <title>Cazlynne Peffer</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_cazlynne_peffer</link>
      <description>Cazlynne Peffer – Muffled Violations (2022) is a sculptural and video-based series exploring sexual trauma through found and used objects, including duvets, chairs, and pantyhose. The works embody the intimate effects of rape, using bodily engagement with materials to convey the lingering impact of trauma. Pantyhose, in particular, references both the body and childhood experiences of boundary-based games, linking notions of consent and violation. Through this practice, Peffer transforms everyday objects into vessels of memory and protest, creating a space for empathy, reflection, and alternative narratives of sexual violence within the South African context. The series acts as a personal and social reckoning, reclaiming meaning and opening paths for healing.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Cazlynne_Peffer.jpg?v=1756733155</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_mika_mrffy</g:id>
      <title>Mika Márffy</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_mika_mrffy</link>
      <description>Zambian-based abstract painter Mika Márffy is inspired by symbolic, transformative change and growth as informed by the unconscious. Mika’s intuitive process-based artworks are layered with meaning, translating energy and emotion and forming a narrative of life beyond what the eye can see. The ‘Sacred Feminine/ Sophia’ is a continual theme in her work.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Mika_Marffy.png?v=1756736128</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_amira_shariff</g:id>
      <title>Amira Shariff</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_amira_shariff</link>
      <description>Amira Shariff (b. 1999, Johannesburg) is an artist, art director, strategist, and cultural curator who primarily works with photography. Currently completing her degree in Strategic Brand Communications at Vega, she also works as a creative strategist in agency and events. A graduate of the Market Photo Workshop (2019) and Through the Lens Collective (2020), her work has been shown at the FNB Art Fair (2022), Berman Contemporary (2021), and the TTL Collective Portrait Show (2020). Inspired by her late uncle, Abdul Shariff, her practice explores identity, connection, and disconnection through layered images that challenge perception.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Amira_Shariff_68db12d5-9d3e-4d1b-95ae-9575234b10e0.jpg?v=1756732279</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_dapaah_gallery</g:id>
      <title>DAPAAH Gallery</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_dapaah_gallery</link>
      <description>Dapaah Gallery is a premier art agency and consultancy specializing in contemporary art from Africa and its global diasporas.The gallery provides expert, assured advice to a diverse clientele, including emerging and established collectors, patrons, and institutions, guiding them in building significant collections. Simultaneously, Dapaah Gallery is dedicated to promoting a curated roster of the most exciting and gifted visual artists of African heritage from around the world, working to elevate their careers and connect their work with a global audience. Positioned at the intersection of advisory and artist representation, Dapaah Gallery is a trusted partner for anyone passionate about the dynamic landscape of art from Africa and its diaspora.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/DAPAAH_Gallery.jpg?v=1756733514</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_kulungwana_art_gallery</g:id>
      <title>Kulungwana Art Gallery</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_kulungwana_art_gallery</link>
      <description>Kulungwana has organized solo and collective art exhibitions, including, painting, sculpture, ceramics and photography. The space has also hosted the launching of books and concerts</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Kulungwana_Art_Gallery.jpg?v=1756735502</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 17:08:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_movart</g:id>
      <title>MOVART</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_movart</link>
      <description>MOVART was founded in 2015 to promote contemporary African art and works by artists from the African and Portuguese-speaking diasporas. With spaces in Luanda (residencies and talent development) and Lisbon (exhibitions and international exposure), the gallery represents artists like IHOSVANNY, KEYEZUA, KWAME SOUSA, MÁRIO MACILAU, RITA GT, and THÓ SIMOES. MOVART participates in major international fairs and offers consultancy for private and corporate collections while producing cultural projects across Africa and Europe.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/MOVART.jpg?v=1756736265</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 17:36:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_reservoir</g:id>
      <title>Reservoir</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_reservoir</link>
      <description>RESERVOIR, founded in 2021 by Heinrich Groenewald and Shona van der Merwe, is a Cape Town-based gallery and curatorial platform. It hosts solo exhibitions, participates in major international art fairs—including Investec Cape Town, ARCO Madrid, SPARK Vienna, and Artissima Turin—and has won awards such as the Investec Emerging Artist Award and Fundación Banco Sabadell Young Talent Award. The gallery also curates collaborative projects, including Mother City (2024), Disrupting the Dream (2025), Spaced Out (Berlin, 2024), and Fallow Ground (Germany, 2024).</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Reservoir.png?v=1756736918</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_white_river_gallery</g:id>
      <title>White River Gallery</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_white_river_gallery</link>
      <description>White River Gallery, established in 2008 and directed by Dana MacFarlane, is a distinctive visual arts platform in the Lowveld. Showcasing contemporary fine art from Mpumalanga as well as broader South and Southern African artists, the gallery highlights regional creativity and the cultural significance of art as social, political, and evolutionary expression. Merging with Halifax Art in 2017, White River Gallery emphasizes personal engagement with clients and collectors, fostering transformative experiences through art.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/White_River_Gallery.jpg?v=1756738088</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_imba_ya_sarai_gallery</g:id>
      <title>Imba Ya Sarai Gallery</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_imba_ya_sarai_gallery</link>
      <description>Imba Ya Sarai is a contemporary art gallery dedicated to showcasing artists from Africa and its global diaspora. Founded to address the challenges faced by even seasoned artists in securing representation, the gallery provides a vital platform for established and emerging voices alike. Through its commitment to inclusivity and sustainability, Imba Ya Sarai connects important African artists with new audiences and collectors, ensuring their continued influence in contemporary art.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Imba_Ya_Sarai_Gallery.jpg?v=1756735009</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 17:00:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_thato_tlatsi</g:id>
      <title>Thato Tlatsi</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_thato_tlatsi</link>
      <description>Tshegofatso Tlatsi (b. 1999, Johannesburg) is a visual artist based in Roodepoort, South Africa. She holds a BA in Fine Arts from the University of Johannesburg (2022) and works primarily in drawing and painting using ink, charcoal, chalk, and acrylic on canvas. Tlatsi’s practice is deeply personal, exploring themes of black femininity, sexuality, mental health, and the complexities of existence. She is particularly drawn to mark-making, embracing the unpredictability of ink and charcoal as metaphors for life, and uses her work to reflect on the interplay between agony, beauty, and free will.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Thato_Tlatsi_32603a75-9bc2-434d-b199-7a8dabb05b29.png?v=1756737806</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_recurate</g:id>
      <title>ReCurate</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_recurate</link>
      <description>Renée Eisen-Khonat is an independent curator and artist based in Gaborone, Botswana, and runs Recurate, a platform dedicated to promoting female, feminist, and emerging contemporary artists. Her experience as an artist informs her curatorial practice, allowing her to understand and support each artist’s unique process. With over 20 years in Botswana’s art scene—as a gallerist, facilitator, and teacher—she is committed to amplifying female artistic voices and developing both artists’ careers and the country’s art market.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/ReCurate.jpg?v=1756736876</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_nada_baraka</g:id>
      <title>Nada Baraka</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_nada_baraka</link>
      <description>Nada Baraka (b. 1990) is a Cairo-based visual artist with a BA in Communication Media Art and Fine Arts from the American University in Cairo and an MFA from Central Saint Martins, London. Her work has been exhibited in London, Paris, Lisbon, and across Cairo, including Gypsum Gallery, Mashrabia Gallery, Darb 1718, and Medrar, and she won first prize in Mohamad Abla’s painting competition in 2015. Baraka’s paintings oscillate between abstraction and surrealism, using vivid colors and expressive brushwork to explore emotional fluctuations and the absurd. Her work often features distorted forms, body parts, and layered compositions, emphasizing fluidity and eruption as a way to narrate complex experiences.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Nada_Baraka.png?v=1756736375</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_sethembile_msezane</g:id>
      <title>Sethembile Msezane</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_sethembile_msezane</link>
      <description>Sethembile Msezane (b. 1991, KwaZulu-Natal) is a Cape Town-based interdisciplinary artist working across photography, painting, live performance, film, sculpture, and installation. Her work explores spirituality, commemoration, African knowledge systems, and the absence of the black female body in historical narratives. Msezane has exhibited widely in South Africa and internationally, including Zeitz MOCAA, Iziko South African National Gallery, The Royal Ontario Museum, and Oscar Niemeyer Museum. She holds an MFA from Michaelis School of Fine Art, UCT, and has participated in residencies, biennales, and received awards including the Rising Light award at the Mbokodo Awards (2016) and recognition as an OkayAfrica 100 Women Honoree (2018).</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Sethembile_Msezane.jpg?v=1756737183</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_christine_dixie</g:id>
      <title>Christine Dixie</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_christine_dixie</link>
      <description>Christine Dixie is an established South African artist whose work explores gender roles, myth, and Europe’s colonial legacy in Africa. Based in Makhanda, she draws on archival imagery and research to create haunting visual narratives that blur the boundaries between past and present. Primarily a printmaker, Dixie often extends her works through embossing, embroidery, books, film, and installation, reflecting her interest in the interplay between text and image. Her art forms part of major collections including The New York Public Library, The Smithsonian National Museum of African Art, The Iwalewahaus Museum, Standard Bank Gallery, Johannesburg Art Gallery, and Iziko South African National Gallery.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Christine_Dixie.jpg?v=1756733348</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 04:24:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_bontle_juku</g:id>
      <title>Bontle Juku</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_bontle_juku</link>
      <description>Bontle Juku is a South African multidisciplinary artist whose practice spans painting, photography, drawing, and experimental film. Her work explores the past and present of Black existence through themes of world-building, spirituality, and socio-political reflection. Using photographic lighting, self-portraiture, and abstraction, Juku creates emotive imagery that reclaims the representation of the Black body with dignity and humanity. Her work is inspired by everyday life, social issues, music, film, and personal experience.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Bontle_Juku.jpg?v=1756732958</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 14:29:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_phila_hillie</g:id>
      <title>Phila Hillie</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_phila_hillie</link>
      <description>Phila Hillie is a multidisciplinary South African artist whose work is inspired by women, culture, and space. Drawing from her background in architecture, digital art, and UI/UX, she explores storytelling, composition, and new media to create spaces—both physical and digital—where women are celebrated and seen.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Phila_Hillie.jpg?v=1756736796</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_buhle_nkalashe</g:id>
      <title>Buhle Nkalashe</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_buhle_nkalashe</link>
      <description>Buhle Nkalashe (b. 1994, South Africa) is a Cape Town-based painter and mixed-media artist working with oil, acrylic, and oil pastels. He holds a BA in Graphic Design from the Cape Town Creative Academy (2018) and transitioned from advertising to full-time visual arts in 2019. Nkalashe draws inspiration from South African cultural ceremonies, particularly Xhosa traditions, using vibrant patterns and colors from Xhosa, Zulu, and Ndebele heritage to create contemporary, hybrid interpretations of African identity.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Buhle_Nkalashe_de041761-66a1-4cd6-8325-3adad1b4691a.jpg?v=1756732994</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_imaan_latif</g:id>
      <title>Imaan Latif</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_imaan_latif</link>
      <description>Imaan Latif is a Johannesburg-based multidimensional artist whose practice spans abstract painting, performance, cultural critique, and playwriting. She is also a personal trainer, spiritual scientist, and Kundalini yoga teacher, working at the intersection of art, academia, and wellness.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Imaan_Latif_6d52a5ce-c177-41b9-b3d8-29529828d33f.jpg?v=1756734981</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_thero_makepe</g:id>
      <title>Thero Makepe</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_thero_makepe</link>
      <description>Thero Makepe (b. 1996, Gaborone, Botswana) is a visual artist whose work reflects personal and societal narratives shaped by his upbringing in Botswana and South Africa. A 2019 BA Photography graduate from the Michaelis School of Fine Art (UCT), Makepe has since gained international recognition, receiving awards and residencies including the Prince Claus Seed Award (2024), FOAM Talent (2024-2025), and the Tierney Fellowship Award (2019). His practice spans photography and multimedia projects, exploring identity, memory, and collective experience. Makepe has presented solo exhibitions such as We Didn’t Choose to Be Down Here (Lemkus Gallery, 2025) and It’s Not Going to Get Better (Vela Projects, 2024–25), alongside participation in prominent group shows locally and abroad, including Art Basel NY and the Botswana Pavilion projects. His work is held in private and public collections, including the University of Cape Town and University of Pretoria. Makepe is a founding member of the Botswana Pavilion collective and works between Gaborone, Cape Town, and Johannesburg.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Thero_Makepe.jpg?v=1756737858</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_candice_myataza</g:id>
      <title>Candice Myataza</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_candice_myataza</link>
      <description>Candice Myataza (b. 1997, Cape Town) is a South African visual artist whose work explores racial belonging and shared human identity. As a mixed-race individual, her paintings reflect on inclusion, community, and the commonalities that connect people beyond race. Graduating with a BA in Film, Anthropology, and Sociology from the University of Cape Town (2021), she works primarily in acrylics, oil, and mixed media on canvas. Myataza has exhibited at Mullers Gallery, 6 Spin Street Gallery, 91 Loop Street Gallery, and Red Gallery in Cape Town, and has sold over 20 paintings. Her style emphasizes earthy tones and intricate line work, inviting reflection on togetherness, spirituality, and shared identity.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Candice_Myataza_559f6038-0351-45b9-9819-90869046e089.png?v=1756733126</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_sarafina_naisula</g:id>
      <title>Sarafina Naisula</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_sarafina_naisula</link>
      <description>Sarafina Naisula (b. 1999) is a contemporary artist of Tanzanian and Dutch heritage. Educated at the University of Arts, London, her work has been exhibited in the Netherlands and South Africa. Naisula explores human identity, particularly the female experience within the African diaspora, using art to challenge preconceptions and spark dialogue. Her current work addresses sexual abuse and the erosion of individual identity, employing silhouettes and layered mediums to highlight the narratives behind statistics and foster awareness, compassion, and social change.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Sarafina_Naisula.png?v=1756737130</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_simone_verfaille</g:id>
      <title>Simone Verfaille</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_simone_verfaille</link>
      <description>Simone Verfaille (b. 1995, Cape Town) is a contemporary artist whose work reflects life’s layers and experiences. She earned a BA(Hons) Fine Art from Stellenbosch University in 2018 and returned to art in 2023 with renewed focus. Her practice uses layered paint to capture memory, time, and personal expression, creating immersive compositions of colour, form, and texture.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Simone_Verfaille.png?v=1756737285</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_tayhe_munsamy</g:id>
      <title>Tayhe Munsamy</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_tayhe_munsamy</link>
      <description>Tayhe Munsamy (b. Johannesburg, South Africa) is a visual artist whose work explores identity, mythology, and folklore through painting, video, performance, and digital media. A Goldsmiths University of London graduate (BA Fine Art and History of Art, First-Class Honours, 2020), Tayhe’s practice reflects her mixed-race heritage and draws from South Africa’s Coloured and Indian communities. Her art blends historical archives with fictional narratives to explore creation, displacement, transformation, and fantasy. Selected for the 2021 RMB Talent Unlocked mentoring program and group exhibition at Everard Read CIRCA Gallery, Tayhe continues to exhibit her work locally and internationally. She is currently based in Johannesburg.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Tayhe_Munsamy.jpg?v=1756737734</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_davina_de_beer</g:id>
      <title>Davina de Beer</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_davina_de_beer</link>
      <description>Davina de Beer (b.1982) is a South African visual artist based in Seville, Spain. She earned her Master’s in Fine Art in 2008 and spent over a decade in Oman, where she taught Art &amp; Design and exhibited widely, including two solo shows in Dubai and Muscat. Since relocating to Spain in 2022, she has been a finalist in the ARTE APARTE contemporary art competition, exhibited at Galeria Zunino, and co-founded the Non-Site Art Collective, debuting their collaboration at the Turbine Art Fair in Johannesburg (2023).</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Davina_de_Beer_35d38ad6-77e1-4aea-ac4e-2c6933a33d8a.png?v=1756733611</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:29:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_flood_house</g:id>
      <title>Flood House</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_flood_house</link>
      <description>Flood House is a creative screen-printing studio. Our focus lies in creative collaboration: working with visual artists, illustrators and designers to create limited edition art prints. Our vision is to promote creative collaboration within the arts by supporting artists and sharing our passion for traditional printmaking. We produce fine art silkscreen prints for clients, both locally and internationally. Check our projects here to see Flood House’s production work. Flood House also co-publishes prints. We join hands with artists to produce limited edition silkscreen prints. View a list of our published works in our shop. Flood House studios are located in Victoria Yards, Johannesburg and is run by artist and printmaker Alexandré Vosloo.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Flood_House.png?v=1756734356</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 08:54:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_gxl__lmad_collection_x_guillotine</g:id>
      <title>GxL - L’MAD Collection x Guillotine</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_gxl__lmad_collection_x_guillotine</link>
      <description>GxL Presents: A Capsule Collection for Giants Introducing an exclusive capsule collection by GxL—the collaboration between L’MAD Collection and Guillotine by Lisa Jaffe. This limited range is designed in celebration of artist Cinthia Sifa Mulanga’s long-awaited solo exhibition, Giants. Drawing inspiration from Mulanga&apos;s powerful new work, the collection channels the artist&apos;s exploration of Black womanhood, inner conflict, and sanctuary. Each piece is crafted from 100% silk and made in South Africa, reflecting the strength and spirit of Mulanga’s art. Pre-Order Information: - This collection is available for pre-order with an expected 7-week delivery time. - Available online at latitudes.online and guillotinebylisajaffe.com.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/GxL_-_L_MAD_Collection_x_Guillotine.jpg?v=1756734728</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:26:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_daynagay_tate</g:id>
      <title>Dayna-Gay Tate</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_daynagay_tate</link>
      <description>Dayna-Gay Tate (b.1994, Zimbabwe/South Africa) is a Cape Town-based artist and visual storyteller working across painting, design, photography, and poetry. A Stellenbosch University graduate (BA Visual Communication Design, Cum Laude, 2017), her practice explores colour, form, and playful abstraction rooted in faith, memory, and storytelling. Through recurring themes of nature, home, light, and time, Tate invites viewers to pause, embrace joy, and reconnect with stillness.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Dayna-Gay_Tate_b161a5aa-3223-453d-961a-403d91543594.jpg?v=1756733651</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_andrew_kayser</g:id>
      <title>Andrew Kayser</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_andrew_kayser</link>
      <description>Andrew Kayser (b. 1975, East London, South Africa) is a Johannesburg-based painter whose work explores suburbia as both a lived habitat and a psychological space. Working primarily in oil, he examines ambiguity, contradiction, and fleeting meaning, creating poignant and melancholic reflections on inner and outer realities. A graduate of the Royal Academy of Art, The Hague (2001), Kayser returned to South Africa in 2005 and resumed his practice after overcoming addiction in 2014. He has since held five solo exhibitions, including Fragments of Longer Stories (Graham Contemporary, 2023), and participated in major fairs such as 1-54 (London), AKAA (Paris), and Investec Cape Town Art Fair. His work is held in both local and international collections.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Andrew_Kayser.png?v=1756732388</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 07:25:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_1616</g:id>
      <title>16/16</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_1616</link>
      <description>16/16, together with the Friends of 16 network, forms an evolving constellation of creators—artists, facilitators, thinkers, and artisans—who coalesce around a shared commitment: building trust, infrastructure, and possibility within Lagos. At our core, 16/16 is both a physical and conceptual aggregator—a site and a catalyst—where ideas, practices, and relationships are free to germinate across disciplines. Since our inception, we have invited members of our carefully curated creative ecosystem (our &apos;Friends of 16&apos;) to activate 16/16 as a centre for mutual learning and collaboration. Through co‐programming, workshops, open studios, residencies and idea prototyping, we&apos;ve transformed the space into a prototype of shelter: simultaneously a safe harbour as well as a creative vantage point, continuously orienting our ever-growing community toward the untold potential of our urban futures.)</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/friends_of_16_logo.png?v=1762501042</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 07:42:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_denzils__jo_art_gallery</g:id>
      <title>Denzil&apos;s &amp; Jo Art Gallery</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_denzils__jo_art_gallery</link>
      <description>Denzil&apos;s and Jo is a contemporary art gallery dedicated to exploring the vibrant and complex world of art from Africa. Our core mission is to challenge the monolithic categorization of &apos;African art&apos; by showcasing the continent&apos;s immense diversity of cultures, histories, and artistic expressions. Through a program of thought-provoking exhibitions, we address important global issues and work to dismantle preconceived notions, promoting a deeper and more nuanced understanding of the continent. The gallery is a nurturing and supportive platform for talented African artists, providing a space for them to share their unique stories, concepts, and journeys. We are committed to fostering their creative growth and amplifying their voices in the ongoing global dialogue about Africa. We invite you to immerse yourself in the captivating perspectives and connect with the artistic excellence that defines contemporary art from Africa.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Denzil_s_Jo_Art_Gallery_thumbnail.jpg?v=1759393675</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_w17_gallery</g:id>
      <title>W17 Gallery</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_w17_gallery</link>
      <description>W17 Gallery, part of Workshop17, reimagines the conventional gallery by merging art with everyday spaces. The gallery activates creativity and dialogue, making art accessible, affordable, and engaging for both artists and collectors. Supporting local and international talent, W17 hosts exhibitions, artist talks, walkabouts, and workshops, while collaborating with galleries, studios, and print workshops. Its services include curation, consultations, and art investment, catering to first-time buyers and seasoned collectors alike.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/W17_Gallery.png?v=1756738037</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_david_madlabane</g:id>
      <title>David Madlabane</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_david_madlabane</link>
      <description>David Madlabane (David Blakc) is a Johannesburg-based visual artist working across drawing, painting, digital art, music, and printmaking techniques such as linocut, silkscreen, and etching. He has assisted at Artist Proof Studio and William Kentridge’s studio, gaining extensive technical experience. Madlabane won first prize in a Cartier collaboration at the FNB Joburg Art Fair, received the People’s Choice Award at the Strauss &amp; Co competition, and was a finalist for the Blessing Ngobeni Art Prize. He continues to build his practice with the ambition of establishing himself internationally.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/David_Madlabane.png?v=1756733565</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_regina_bardavid</g:id>
      <title>Regina Bardavid</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_regina_bardavid</link>
      <description>Regina Bardavid is a Johannesburg-based artist whose work explores abstract expressionism through vibrant, non-figurative forms. Inspired by meditation, intuition, and everyday patterns—like coffee remnants—her paintings are spontaneous explorations that evoke emotion and imagination.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Regina_Bardavid.png?v=1756736913</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_mbali_shabane</g:id>
      <title>Mbali Shabane</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_mbali_shabane</link>
      <description>Mbalenhle Shabane (b. 1990, Durban) is a South African artist and emerging curator whose work explores the female journey through themes of identity, spirituality, trauma, and healing. A Fine Arts graduate from Durban University of Technology, she launched Change Room (2019), a collaborative project fostering dialogue among womxn. Her work was recently featured in Durban: A Curatorial Journey (2024) at The Pencil Club.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Mbali_Shabane.png?v=1756736078</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_wunika_mukan_gallery</g:id>
      <title>Wunika Mukan Gallery</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_wunika_mukan_gallery</link>
      <description>Wunika Mukan Gallery, formerly Pacers, is a contemporary art gallery in Lagos, Nigeria, founded in 2020 by Wunika Mukan. The gallery champions emerging artists from Nigeria, Sub-Saharan Africa, and the diaspora, providing a platform for local and international exposure and engagement with the wider art market. Committed to innovation and artistic excellence, Wunika Mukan Gallery supports experimentation with new ideas, techniques, and mediums, establishing itself as a key force in Nigeria’s contemporary art scene.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Wunika_Mukan_Gallery.png?v=1756738140</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_bode</g:id>
      <title>BODE</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_bode</link>
      <description>Bode is a contemporary gallery with spaces in Berlin and Havana, dedicated to collaborating with a diverse and international group of artists. The gallery&apos;s program focuses on practices that explore and challenge traditional notions of representation. Through concept, medium, and aesthetics, the artists we work with push the boundaries of contemporary art across a wide range of disciplines. In addition to its exhibition schedule, Bode is committed to fostering creative dialogue through an artist-in-residence program and collaborations with curators, institutions, and other partners worldwide.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/BODE.png?v=1756732897</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_afriart_gallery</g:id>
      <title>Afriart Gallery</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_afriart_gallery</link>
      <description>Founded in Kampala in 2002, Afriart Gallery (AAG) has grown into a leading international voice for contemporary art from the African continent. We are dedicated to showcasing original forms of expression and creating a dynamic environment where collectors can engage with powerful artistic ideas and discussions. Our gallery was established by artist Daudi Karungi, whose firsthand experience informs our artist-centric mission. We are deeply committed to building a supportive and equitable community, actively fostering our artists&apos; careers through dedicated mentorship, strategic visibility, and diligent archiving of their work. This commitment has successfully launched our artists onto the world stage. Works by AAG artists are consistently featured in major museums, biennales, and the world&apos;s most prestigious art fairs, including Art Basel Miami Beach, EXPO Chicago, Art Paris, 1:54 Contemporary African Art Fair, and FNB Art Joburg, among many others.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Afriart_thumbnail.png?v=1758193049</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_this_is_not_a_white_cube-2</g:id>
      <title>THIS IS NOT A WHITE CUBE</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_this_is_not_a_white_cube-2</link>
      <description>THIS IS NOT A WHITE CUBE is a contemporary art gallery based in Luanda and Lisbon, representing emerging and established artists from Africa, its diaspora, and the Global South. The gallery fosters intercultural dialogue through both in-gallery and off-site exhibitions, highlighting themes like identity, memory, and social change. Founded by Sónia Ribeiro and Graça Rodrigues, it also runs O CUBO, a non-profit supporting residencies, research, and international collaborations. The gallery participates in exhibitions worldwide, promoting experimentation and global engagement.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/THIS_IS_NOT_A_WHITE_CUBE.png?v=1756737936</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_affinity_gallery</g:id>
      <title>Affinity Gallery</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_affinity_gallery</link>
      <description>Based in Lagos, Nigeria, Affinity Art Gallery is a contemporary art space founded in 2020 with a mission to champion the next generation of artists from Africa and its diaspora. We are deeply committed to providing a platform where emerging talent can explore creative ideas across all mediums, without boundaries. Through a dynamic program of curated exhibitions, participation in international art fairs, and engaging educational initiatives, we offer collectors, museums, and foundations unique access to an incredible selection of artists. Our ultimate purpose is to accelerate our artists&apos; careers on the global stage, sharing the rich cultural heritage of Africa and inspiring future generations.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Affinity_thumbnail.png?v=1758192945</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 08:32:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_adeyosola_adeniran</g:id>
      <title>Adeyosola Adeniran</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_adeyosola_adeniran</link>
      <description>Adeyosola Adeniran, an artist and curator based in Lagos, Nigeria, currently serves as Curatorial Assistant at the African Artists&apos; Foundation and LagosPhoto Festival. Her curatorial practice is based on close collaboration with artists to realise and/or present their best work.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Adeyosola_Adeniran.png?v=1756732042</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 11:59:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_baoagi_keitshokile</g:id>
      <title>Baoagi Keitshokile</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_baoagi_keitshokile</link>
      <description>Baoagi One Keitshokile is a multidisciplinary artist from Serowe, Botswana. Immersed in cultural and performing arts from a young age, he later studied art and design, cultivating a practice that spans visual art, poetry, music, and curation. A member of the Art of the Poets collective since 2007, he has showcased work across Botswana, South Africa, and Zimbabwe. Based at Khama III Memorial Museum, where he manages a studio and assists with exhibitions, Baoagi also adjudicates national arts competitions. His practice, rooted in versatility, centres on enlightenment as empowerment, using art to inspire positivity and confront social challenges.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Baoagi_Keitshokile.png?v=1756732638</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 12:18:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_bayron_van_wyk</g:id>
      <title>Bayron Van Wyk</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_bayron_van_wyk</link>
      <description>Bayron Van Wyk is a writer, researcher, and cultural worker. He holds a BA (Hons) from the University of Namibia and an MA in Anthropology from the University of the Western Cape. Since 2022, he has worked with the Museums Association of Namibia, engaging with Namibian collections and their colonial histories. His work focuses on restitution, provenance research, and artistic engagement with cultural objects to promote ethical practices in heritage and museum spaces.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Bayron_Van_Wyk.png?v=1756732711</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_giancarlo_laguerta</g:id>
      <title>Giancarlo LaGuerta</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_giancarlo_laguerta</link>
      <description>Giancarlo Diablo LaGuerta is a self-taught multidisciplinary artist and curator based in Gaborone, Botswana. His work spans painting, drawing, collage, photography, video, and music, exploring politics, masculinity, culture, and heritage. Giancarlo often creates large-scale, experimental pieces that blur representation and abstraction, amplifying personal and collective experiences of emotion, grief, and societal issues.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Giancarlo_LaGuerta.png?v=1756734556</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_kamogelo_sebopa</g:id>
      <title>Kamogelo Sebopa</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_kamogelo_sebopa</link>
      <description>Kamogelo Sebopa is a Johannesburg based emerging artist and curator. Sebopa recently obtained her degree in BA Fine Art program at the University of the Witwatersrand. Sebopa is currently interested in drawing and printmaking and furthering her curatorial practice. She was recently shortlisted and won the CCAC student competition for printmaking.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Kamogelo_Sebopa.png?v=1756735173</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_kukua_kwekubadu</g:id>
      <title>Kukua Kweku-Badu</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_kukua_kwekubadu</link>
      <description>Kukua Kweku-Badu is an independent curator and poet exploring decolonial and queer alternate realities within global contemporary art. Their work centers on amplifying the narratives of queer/trans-Indigenous individuals from the Global South and diaspora, while reimagining ways of presenting and engaging with art. Kukua holds a BA in Communications Studies from the Ghana Institute of Journalism and has experience in media, marketing, and artist support.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Kukua_Kweku-Badu.png?v=1756735443</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_ngonga_silupya</g:id>
      <title>Ng&apos;onga Silupya</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_ngonga_silupya</link>
      <description>Ng’onga Silupya (b. 1996, Lusaka, Zambia) is a cultural practitioner, curator, and arts administrator. Her work explores the intersections of cultural heritage, contemporary art, and social, environmental, and political issues. She currently serves as Administrator and Assistant Curator at the Lusaka Contemporary Art Centre and has extensive experience with the Zambia National Visual Arts Council and Lechwe Trust Art Gallery.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Ng_onga_Silupya.png?v=1756736551</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_onyinye_alheri</g:id>
      <title>Onyinye Alheri</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_onyinye_alheri</link>
      <description>Onyịnye Alheri is a multidisciplinary artist and curator born in Lagos, Nigeria and living in southern Africa. At the core of Ọ’s practice is an exploration into the depths of consciousness and existence. Alheri is a member of Aguas Migrantes, a collective composed of interdisciplinary artists across continents.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Onyinye_Alheri.png?v=1756736734</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_raelee_seymourbrown</g:id>
      <title>Raelee Seymour-Brown</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_raelee_seymourbrown</link>
      <description>Raelee Seymour-Brown is a Johannesburg-based multimedia artist, designer, and curator. Her work explores the unseen within pop culture, transforming the mundane into thought-provoking experiences across digital illustration, writing, ceramics, fashion, and design. Through diverse mediums, she investigates the complexities of contemporary life with irreverence and curiosity.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Raelee_Seymour-Brown.png?v=1756736860</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_chlo_shain</g:id>
      <title>Chloë Shain</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_chlo_shain</link>
      <description>Chloë Shain (b. 1993, Johannesburg) is a multidisciplinary artist and anthropologist. She holds an Honours in Fine Art from Wits University and a PhD in Anthropology from the University of Cape Town. Shain works across painting, digital collage, video animation, and installation, exploring human relationships with mobile devices through touchscreen gestures. Her recent exhibitions include Nirox Sculpture Park, NewWork22 at Wits Art Museum, and the Turbine Art Fair, where she was selected for the 2023 Unearthed mentorship programme.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Chloe_Shain_f66ce87a-f359-4263-a5f7-82ba1264bb5e.png?v=1756733342</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_chuma_adam</g:id>
      <title>Chuma Adam</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_chuma_adam</link>
      <description>Chuma Adam (b. 2001) is a Johannesburg-based multidisciplinary artist working across painting, printmaking, textiles, sculpture, and drawing. Influenced by Édouard Glissant’s Poetics of Relation, her practice engages themes of visibility, Blackness, and self-actualization through abstraction, texture, and mark-making. Mixing earth from her mother’s home into her work, Adam creates immersive pieces that explore the intersections of Blackness, womanhood, and African artistic lineage. She holds an Honours degree in Fine Arts from Wits University (2024) and was shortlisted for the WITS Young Artist Award in 2022 and 2023.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Chuma_Adam_c109c4be-0223-41f0-84e9-2e892787f399.png?v=1756733461</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 04:25:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_kutti_collective</g:id>
      <title>Kutti Collective</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_kutti_collective</link>
      <description>Kutti Collective is a group of six young South African artists of South Asian ancestry who challenge social norms while redefining identity and representation. Reclaiming the word Kutti—which can mean both “bitch” and “darling” across South Asian languages—they subvert its patriarchal weight to assert power and agency. Their work reflects on ancestry, lived experiences, and traumas, complicating ideas of what it means to be South Asian and ‘Indian’ today.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Kutti_Collective.png?v=1756735528</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 04:24:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_marielorraine_kalassa</g:id>
      <title>Marie-Lorraine Kalassa</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_marielorraine_kalassa</link>
      <description>Marie-Lorraine Kalassa is a South African artist of Congolese descent whose work explores identity, ancestry, and notions of home. Using personal archives, reflexive writing, and diverse media, she investigates how memory, place, and culture shape selfhood and belonging. Kalassa holds a Fine Arts degree from Michaelis School of Fine Arts and an Honours in Landscape Architecture from the University of Cape Town. She is a member of The Photographic Collective (TPC) and has exhibited in shows including JIVE Exhibition (2023), We Are Culture (2022), and 1-54 Contemporary African Art Fair (London, 2021).</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Marie-Lorraine_Kalassa.png?v=1756735961</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_nathaniel_sheppard_iii</g:id>
      <title>Nathaniel Sheppard III</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_nathaniel_sheppard_iii</link>
      <description>Nathaniel Sheppard III (b. 1989) is a Johannesburg-based printmaker, painter, and collage artist. Trained at WITS and David Krut Projects, his practice combines printmaking, painting, and found imagery to explore culture, politics, and identity. In 2016, he co-founded Danger Gevaar Ingozi Studio, a collective rooted in independent publishing and printmaking’s social value.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Nathaniel_Sheppard_III.png?v=1756736483</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_sahlah_davids</g:id>
      <title>Sahlah Davids</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_sahlah_davids</link>
      <description>Sahlah Davids (b. 1998, Cape Town) is a mixed media artist working with textiles and beadwork. A graduate of UCT (2020), her practice explores the intertwined histories of religion, politics, and heritage within the Cape Muslim community. Drawing on the skills of her seamstress grandmother and tailor grandfather, Davids transforms traditional craft into a quiet act of protest and a visual archive of resilience, spirituality, and generational struggle.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Sahlah_Davids.png?v=1756737012</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_tamary_kudita</g:id>
      <title>Tamary Kudita</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_tamary_kudita</link>
      <description>Tamary Kudita is a multi-award-winning Zimbabwean fine art photographer, scholar, and visual artist exploring African identity, cultural duality, and transgenerational memory. A Michaelis School of Fine Art graduate (BFA, 2017), she gained international recognition as the first African to win the 2021 Open Photographer of the Year at the Sony World Photography Awards for her series African Victorian. Kudita’s work has been exhibited globally, including Art Basel Miami, Sharjah Xposure, Investec Cape Town Art Fair, and Photo Vogue Festival Milan. Her accolades include the J.M.D Manyika Fellowship (Harvard, 2023), See Me Art Takes Runner Up (2021), and honorable mentions from the International Photography Awards. Her art is held in prestigious collections, including the Fitchburg Art Museum (USA) and The Betsy Gallery (Florida), and has been featured in international media such as BBC, CNN, Forbes, and Vogue Italia.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Tamary_Kudita.png?v=1756737724</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_salon_kewpie</g:id>
      <title>Salon Kewpie</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_salon_kewpie</link>
      <description>Salon Kewpie: The Legacy Project is an interdisciplinary platform providing queer and disadvantaged youth with creative access to the themes embodied in the Kewpie Collection. The initiative bridges contemporary ballroom culture with a rich historical photographic archive, centred on the life of Kewpie Fritz (1941–2012) — a celebrated hairdresser, performer, and fearless queer icon of apartheid-era District Six. Through workshops led by experts in activism, mental health, ballroom culture, and drag artistry, the programme nurtures personal and artistic growth while reclaiming histories of resilience, freedom, and belonging. The culmination of this journey is the Salon Kewpie: The Legacy Ball — a vibrant celebration uniting youth, queer and trans elders, and the District Six community in honour of Kewpie’s enduring spirit. Bringing Kewpie’s legacy home to District Six.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Salon_Kewpie.png?v=1756737046</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 14:38:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_andrea_burgener</g:id>
      <title>Andrea Burgener</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_andrea_burgener</link>
      <description>Andrea Burgener (MAFA, Wits) is a Johannesburg-based artist, chef and food writer whose practice merges artmaking with research into the politics of food. Working with diverse media—from paint and animation to food packaging and cake—she explores themes of land, power, consumption, and culpability with wit and sharp critique. Recurring motifs like chef toques, rats, and phosphorescent objects trace connections between agriculture, warfare, and globalised food systems, questioning the ethics of consumption and the invisibility of labour in industrial production.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Andrea_Burgener.png?v=1756732350</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_occupying_the_gallery</g:id>
      <title>Occupying The Gallery</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_occupying_the_gallery</link>
      <description>Occupying the Gallery is a visual arts project, mentorship program, mobile studio, and artist residency founded in July 2023 by Mary Sibande and Lawrence Lemaoana. It collaborates with emerging artists—called “Occupants”—to produce experimental and immersive exhibitions, transforming gallery spaces into interactive experiences. The initiative spans diverse media, fostering dialogue around identity, space, and culture while bridging access to industry, professional growth, and opportunities for young artists.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Occupying_The_Gallery.png?v=1756736692</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_candice_berman_gallery</g:id>
      <title>Candice Berman Gallery</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_candice_berman_gallery</link>
      <description>Since 2013, Candice Berman Gallery has been a premier destination in Johannesburg for fine art collectors. Guided by a deep curiosity for the cultural and personal narratives behind art, the gallery represents a diverse collection of media with a primary focus on the Expressionist Movement. The gallery is founded on a commitment to supporting the development of its artists, creating novel opportunities for their work to be shared both locally and internationally. We consider it our privilege to connect collectors with exceptional raw talent and unique, compelling pieces. Beyond its exhibition program, Candice Berman Gallery offers a complete suite of services. Our expert consultants collaborate with clients to build unique collections, while our highly trained team provides professional installation. We also offer custom, museum-quality framing as a certified Guild-Commended Framer, ensuring the highest standard of care for your artworks. We invite you to visit our regularly hosted exhibitions to discover the artists shaping the contemporary art landscape.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Candice_Berman_Gallery.png?v=1756733065</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_yenwa_gallery</g:id>
      <title>Yenwa Gallery</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_yenwa_gallery</link>
      <description>Yenwa Gallery, founded in 2021 by curator and designer Ugonna Ibe, is a contemporary gallery in Lagos, Nigeria, representing emerging and mid-career artists across Africa and its diaspora. With a focus on women in photography and new media, the gallery showcases work exploring identity, spirituality, culture, and socio-economic themes. Since opening in April 2023, Yenwa Gallery has emphasized community, innovation, and dialogue, supporting artists through exhibitions, collaborations, educational initiatives, and participation in international art fairs.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Yenwa_Gallery.png?v=1756738349</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_untitled_art</g:id>
      <title>Untitled Art</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_untitled_art</link>
      <description>Untitled creates accessible and inclusive spaces for people to discover, explore, and buy art. Since launching in 2020, the platform has engaged audiences through studio visits, digital content, and participation in fairs like Investec Cape Town Art Fair (ALT) and FNB Art Joburg (LAB). Focusing on authentic connections, Untitled works with both emerging and established South African artists to foster meaningful engagement between artists, collectors, and art lovers.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Untitled_Art.png?v=1756737993</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_nelson_makamo_studio</g:id>
      <title>Nelson Makamo Studio</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_nelson_makamo_studio</link>
      <description>Nelson Makamo is a Johannesburg-based artist from Limpopo, South Africa, celebrated for his compelling portraits of African children that capture resilience, beauty, and emotion. Working across charcoal, acrylic, print, and watercolor, his storytelling emphasizes spontaneity and expressive mark-making. Trained at Artist Proof Studios, Makamo draws influence from Dumile Feni, Picasso, and Van Gogh. His work has been exhibited internationally—in South Africa, the USA, France, Italy, the Netherlands, England, and Scotland—and is included in prestigious collections worldwide. Makamo has also gained mainstream recognition, appearing on The Daily Show with Trevor Noah and on the cover of Time magazine, while mentoring young African artists and reshaping global perceptions of African childhood.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Nelson_Makamo_Studio.png?v=1756736525</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 17:42:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_keabetse_maake</g:id>
      <title>Keabetse Maake</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_keabetse_maake</link>
      <description>Keabetse Maake is a multidisciplinary artist from Tembisa, Gauteng. Working across textile art, printmaking, photography, design, and performance, she is best known for her vibrant yarn paintings that weave stories of Black joy, fantasy, and identity. Rooted in her experiences and cultural background, Maake’s work celebrates the exuberance of youth while exploring the complexities of African heritage and belonging.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Keabetse_Maake_3853c3a3-4be9-453d-8cbe-ff89d4b54bab.jpg?v=1756735266</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_lemkus_gallery</g:id>
      <title>Lemkus Gallery</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_lemkus_gallery</link>
      <description>Lemkus Gallery, located in the Exchange Building on St George’s Mall, was founded in 2024 to host and support the Residency28 programme — an initiative providing emerging local artists with studio space, funding, and professional support to develop sustainable creative practices. Backed by Lemkus and PayJustNow, the residency offers five weeks of studio access, a stipend for materials and living expenses, mentorship, and culminates in a solo exhibition at the gallery. Beyond the residency, Lemkus Gallery functions as a dynamic project space, hosting group shows and experimental exhibitions to foster collaboration and community within Cape Town’s arts scene.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Lemkus_Gallery.png?v=1756735684</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 17:15:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_amasaka_gallery</g:id>
      <title>Amasaka Gallery</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_amasaka_gallery</link>
      <description>Amasaka Gallery is a dynamic contemporary art space in Masaka, Uganda, established in 2020 by artist Collin Sekajugo. The gallery is dedicated to showcasing and nurturing the region&apos;s most promising emerging artistic talent. Born from Sekajugo&apos;s acclaimed Weaver Bird Residency program, Amasaka Gallery&apos;s founding mission is to provide mentorship, support, and a platform for experimentation. It fosters a creative environment where local and regional artists are encouraged to push the boundaries of their practice, from painting and photography to installation. With a satellite space in Kampala and a network of international collaborations, Amasaka is actively redefining the regional art scene and inviting the global art world to look beyond its traditional centres. Through its ambitious program of exhibitions, art fair participation, and collaborative projects, the gallery has quickly established itself as a vital contributor to both local and international art communities.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Amasaka_Gallery_thumbnail.png?v=1758194377</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_isabella_maake</g:id>
      <title>Isabella Maake</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_isabella_maake</link>
      <description>Isabella Maake is a South African contemporary visual artist who, living with profound hearing loss, uses art to explore identity, duality, and vulnerability through portraiture and figurative work. A multidisciplinary practitioner, she works in painting, photography, sculpture, and interactive sound. Isabella has exhibited at the 1-54 Contemporary African Art Fair (London) and in Polokwane, South Africa. In 2023, she received a Chevening Scholarship and is pursuing a master’s in Fine Art at Oxford.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Isabella_Maake_69e682ce-7002-469f-b654-62aee46720a8.png?v=1756735040</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_yaknoabasi_jessicah_ene</g:id>
      <title>Yaknoabasi Jessicah Ene</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_yaknoabasi_jessicah_ene</link>
      <description>Yakno-Abasi Ene is a Lagos-based abstract realism artist whose work explores sisterhood, women’s empowerment, and the divine feminine. Inspired by the strong women in her family, she celebrates unity, resilience, and grace through her art, using diverse mediums to reflect her personal experiences and evolving imagination. Her practice seeks to educate, heal, and inspire, highlighting the strength and beauty of women in contemporary society.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Yaknoabasi_Jessicah_Ene.png?v=1756738250</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_leeann_olwage</g:id>
      <title>Lee-Ann Olwage</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_leeann_olwage</link>
      <description>Lee-Ann Olwage is a South African visual storyteller whose collaborative photography explores themes of gender and identity. With a background in film directing and set design, she creates affirming, narrative-driven imagery that celebrates her subjects’ agency. Her acclaimed project The Right To Play highlights the barriers girls face in accessing education while imagining empowering, playful futures where they thrive. Olwage’s work has appeared in National Geographic, Vogue, The Guardian, and Foam Magazine. She is a multi-award-winning artist, with honours including the World Press Photo Award (2020, 2023, 2024) and the Sony World Photography Award (2023).</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Lee-Ann_Olwage.png?v=1756735644</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_marie_aime_fattouche</g:id>
      <title>Marie Aimée Fattouche</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_marie_aime_fattouche</link>
      <description>Marie Aimée Fattouche (b. 1991, lives and works in Seine-Saint-Denis, France) is a multidisciplinary artist whose work explores the mechanics of mind, body, and environment. Drawing from her Egyptian heritage, she examines power structures, femininity, and collective belief systems through fluid, ever-evolving compositions that blur the boundaries between rupture and repair. A graduate of Chelsea College of Arts, London (MA Fine Art, 2016), Fattouche has received several accolades, including the Mercers’ Arts Award and the Red Mansion Art Prize. Her work has been exhibited internationally at venues such as the Museum of Modern and Contemporary Art (MAMC+), Standpoint Gallery, and Galerie du Haut-Pavé, where she presented her solo show NOUS INFINIR MON AMOUR in 2024.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Marie_Aimee_Fattouche.png?v=1756736003</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_silindokuhle_shandu</g:id>
      <title>Silindokuhle Shandu</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_silindokuhle_shandu</link>
      <description>Silindokuhle Shandu (b. 1998, Johannesburg) is a multidisciplinary artist whose work explores womanhood, identity, and the contrasts between urban, suburban, and rural South Africa. Drawing on her upbringing in Empangeni and eMalahleni, she uses color, texture, and composition to reflect on belonging, otherness, and personal journey. She holds a diploma in Fashion Design and Technology from Tshwane University of Technology.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Silindokuhle_Shandu.jpg?v=1756737237</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_southern_guild</g:id>
      <title>Southern Guild</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_southern_guild</link>
      <description>Southern Guild, founded in 2008 by Trevyn and Julian McGowan, represents contemporary African artists from the continent and diaspora, with locations in Cape Town and Los Angeles. The gallery supports artists exploring culture, spirituality, identity, ancestral knowledge, and ecology through collaborative projects, exhibitions, and its GUILD Residency programme. Southern Guild fosters emerging talent via education, mentorship, and interdisciplinary initiatives, while participating in international fairs and biennales. Its artists’ works are held in major collections, including the Metropolitan Museum of Art, LACMA, Art Institute of Chicago, Pérez Art Museum, and Vitra Museum, and have exhibited at institutions such as Centre Pompidou, Brooklyn Museum, Seoul Museum of Art, and Cooper Hewitt Smithsonian Design Museum.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Southern_Guild.jpg?v=1756737565</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_queens_brussels</g:id>
      <title>Queens Brussels</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_queens_brussels</link>
      <description>Queens Brussels is a multidisciplinary art space housed in a historic mansion, showcasing painting, photography, sculpture, video, performance, and digital art. The gallery supports artist residencies, providing visibility and flexible spaces for creative development. Its intimate Louis XVI-style rooms also host chamber concerts, jazz performances, and jam sessions, creating a vibrant cultural hub.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Queens_Brussels.jpg?v=1756736835</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_sarah_jayne_fell</g:id>
      <title>Sarah Jayne Fell</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_sarah_jayne_fell</link>
      <description>Sarah Jayne Fell (b. 1986, Cape Town) is a painter whose work explores personal myth through expressionism and process art, with a focus on colour and light. Drawing on dreams, journaling, and freestyle painting, her practice is autobiographical and cathartic, blending painting, digital collage, and poetry. Fell began creating art in her mother’s ceramic studio in KwaZulu-Natal and later studied creative writing, media, philosophy, and literature. She has exhibited at the KZNSA, ANON. Pop Up, and Zeitz MOCAA, and currently works from her studio in Kommetjie, Cape Town.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Sarah_Jayne_Fell.png?v=1756737173</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_yasmine_amal</g:id>
      <title>Yasmine Amal</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_yasmine_amal</link>
      <description>Yasmine Amal is a self-taught German-Moroccan artist and political scientist. Her work explores ancestral connection, intersectional feminism, and the meaning of Indigeneity. Drawing inspiration from the ocean and Amazigh symbolism, she creates paintings that reflect harmony, heritage, and collective responsibility. Currently an art fellow at laba Berlin and Künstlerhaus Bethanien, she uses art to foster cross-cultural dialogue and shared values.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Yasmine_Amal.png?v=1756738316</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_mpumi_mayisa</g:id>
      <title>Mpumi Mayisa</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_mpumi_mayisa</link>
      <description>Mpumi Mayisa is a Johannesburg-based curator, cultural worker, and art writer focused on archives and memory. Her work explores personal and collective histories, creating dialogues between past and present through exhibitions such as Bathini Abafazi? and A Crescendo of DayDreams. Mpumi is also the founder of Among The Lilies, a creative platform supporting artistic practice and community engagement.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Mpumi_Mayisa.png?v=1756736293</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_hanien_conradie</g:id>
      <title>Hanien Conradie</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_hanien_conradie</link>
      <description>Hanien Conradie is a South African earth artist whose work combines painting, performance, and natural pigments to explore human-nature relationships. She holds an MFA from Michaelis School of Fine Art, UCT, and draws inspiration from landscapes across Southern Africa and Botswana. Her work, including landscape paintings and organic installations, has been exhibited locally and internationally, with solo shows such as Raaswater (2019) and Spoorloos (2021), and group exhibitions including Earth Power! (2022, Brussels) and 1-54 London. Conradie’s practice encourages reflection on humanity’s connection to nature.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Hanien_Conradie_9456845b-1f7f-4272-8c9d-783e3cb40a2e.png?v=1756734788</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_blessing_blaai</g:id>
      <title>Blessing Blaai</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_blessing_blaai</link>
      <description>Blessing N Blaai (b. 1994, Johannesburg) is an artist whose practice spans painting, drawing, printmaking, and mural art. Rooted in the suburban landscape of Troyeville, his work reflects a deep engagement with community and urban space. A graduate of Artist Proof Studio, where he specialised in printmaking, Blaai has developed a versatile practice that includes watercolour, ink, and mixed media. As a muralist, he has contributed to public and private commissions, including city-commissioned projects that transform urban environments. His work has been featured in group exhibitions such as African Mobilities: This Is Not a Refugee Camp. Dedicated to art as a tool for connection, Blaai has also facilitated community arts programs with the Market Foundation at Windybrow Theatre, creating creative outlets for children in Hillbrow and beyond.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Blessing_Blaai.png?v=1756732843</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:55:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_lerato_motaung</g:id>
      <title>Lerato Motaung</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_lerato_motaung</link>
      <description>Lerato Motaung (b. 1991, Germiston) is a Johannesburg-based multidisciplinary artist whose practice explores memory, identity, and collective narratives. Through expressive color and layered compositions, Motaung reflects on the emotional weight of remembrance, transformation, and resilience. He holds a National Diploma in Fine Art from Tshwane University of Technology and was a finalist in the 2021 Sasol New Signatures Awards. His international recognition includes the Our Africa, Our Future residency in Senegal (2022) and exhibitions at Christie&apos;s Paris, Haart Gallery London, THK Gallery Cologne, and the Pretoria Art Museum. Motaung’s work forms part of major collections including Foundation H (Paris and Madagascar) and Africa First.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Lerato_Motaung.png?v=1756735731</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_simon_venter</g:id>
      <title>Simon Venter</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_simon_venter</link>
      <description>Simon Venter is a multidisciplinary artist whose practice bridges traditional fine arts and emerging technologies. With a foundation in classical oil painting, he incorporates AI to explore creativity, human agency, and the impact of technology on artistic expression. Drawing from global traditions and South African visual storytelling, Venter’s work examines existential themes, archetypes, and the tension between history and innovation. He has exhibited locally and internationally and holds a Master’s in Creative Media and Production.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Simon_Venter.png?v=1756737336</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_lugra_ilunga</g:id>
      <title>Lugra Ilunga</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_lugra_ilunga</link>
      <description>Lugra Israel Ilunga (b.1995, Lubumbashi, DRC) is a Johannesburg-based mixed-media artist exploring masculinity in contemporary society. Using ink, charcoal, collage, and oil pastels, he examines societal pressures on men through cityscapes, landmarks, and symbolic objects. Ilunga has exhibited locally and integrates human rights themes into his work alongside his law degree from the University of Johannesburg.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Lugra_Ilunga.png?v=1756735835</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_karin_preller</g:id>
      <title>Karin Preller</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_karin_preller</link>
      <description>Karin Preller is a Johannesburg-based artist whose work transforms everyday snapshots into haunting reflections on memory and time. A former lawyer with a PhD in Art and Design from the University of Johannesburg, her paintings explore the tension between remembrance and loss. Preller has exhibited widely, with Beyond Memory (2022) earning the KKNK KANNA Award and a KykNET Fiësta nomination. Her work is held in major South African collections, including the Johannesburg Art Gallery and ABSA.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Karin_Preller_e78c3772-a1b8-40e9-8b1f-c9b99b93dd82.jpg?v=1756735178</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_adaruth_kellow</g:id>
      <title>Ada-Ruth Kellow</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_adaruth_kellow</link>
      <description>Ada-Ruth Kellow (b. 1957, Germany) is a Johannesburg-based figurative painter. Working in the tradition of social critique, her art confronts uncomfortable truths through realistic rendering, rich symbolism, and ornamental detail. Kellow holds a BA Honours in Fine Arts (with distinction) from Wits University and was a 2024 finalist for the prestigious Rust-en-Vrede Portrait Award. Her work invites viewers to uncover complex narratives that balance confrontation with moments of dark humour and consolation.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Ada-Ruth_Kellow_thubmnail.png?v=1758192308</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_sam_kentridge</g:id>
      <title>Sam Kentridge</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_sam_kentridge</link>
      <description>Sam Kentridge (b. 1992, Johannesburg) is an artist whose work revolves around language, fragmented text, and collage, exploring how meaning is constructed and disrupted. A former high school English and History teacher, Sam draws on his fascination with narrative, humor, and everyday absurdities. His work has been featured in group exhibitions at The Gallery (Johannesburg), Turbine Art Fair (2022), and Latitudes Art Fair (2023).</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Sam_Kentridge.jpg?v=1756737087</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_kulnzu</g:id>
      <title>KulnZu</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_kulnzu</link>
      <description>kulnZu (b. 1998) is a Mozambican artist and scholar based in Nairobi, Kenya. Working across photography, collage, and writing, their practice explores queerness and tender representations of queer intimacy and masculinities. They hold a B.A. in Africana Studies from Pomona College and are pursuing an MSc in African Studies at the University of Oxford. Their research and art engage with queer urban cultural production, mobility, and the imagining of ‘afroqueer futurity’—envisioning queer lives, bodies, and belonging through creative practice.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/KulnZu.png?v=1756735487</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_banana_club</g:id>
      <title>Banana Club</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_banana_club</link>
      <description>BANANA CLUB is an interdisciplinary artistic collective founded in 2019 to foster critical discourse at the intersection of contemporary art, design, film, and human rights. Our core mission is to amplify marginalized voices and build sustainable career opportunities for emerging artists. Through a dynamic program of art residencies, community dialogues, and art education initiatives, we serve as a vital platform for cultural exchange and innovation. Based in Botswana, we are dedicated to championing the nation&apos;s burgeoning contemporary arts ecosystem while strategically positioning its artists and thinkers within broader African and global conversations.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Banana_Club_thumbnail.png?v=1758196035</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_tbp_artist_collective</g:id>
      <title>TBP Artist Collective</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_tbp_artist_collective</link>
      <description>TBP Artist Collective (formerly The Botswana Pavilion) is a Botswana-based artist platform founded in 2019, comprising Kim Karabo Makin, LegakwanaLeo Makgekgenene, Rrangwane, Thebe Phetogo, and Thero Makepe. The collective champions Botswana’s creative development and archives its artistic practices, addressing under-representation locally and internationally. Drawing inspiration from national pavilions at global events, TBP bridges fine art, visual art, and traditional crafts. Its projects include exhibitions like No Return (Gallery MOMO, 2019), Subjective Nationhood (Botswana National Art Gallery, 2019), the virtual Collective Ties (2020), and Maš(w)i a Ditoro (tsa Rona) (Frankfurt, 2022). TBP also produced the video Kgolokwe: Separated Intersections, screened internationally in Basel, New York, Cape Town, São Paulo, and Berlin.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/TBP_Artist_Collective.png?v=1756737750</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_the_space_botswana</g:id>
      <title>The Space Botswana</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_the_space_botswana</link>
      <description>Located in the heart of Maun, The Space Botswana is a dynamic art gallery and creative hub, housed in a repurposed shipping container—symbolizing resilience and artistic innovation. Established in 2019, it serves as a platform for local and international artists, fostering collaboration and cultural exchange. Beyond exhibitions, it offers a makers-space for sculptors and designers, as well as immersive art retreats that blend creativity with the natural beauty of the Okavango Delta. A true sanctuary for artists and art enthusiasts alike, The Space Botswana is redefining the creative landscape of Southern Africa.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/The_Space_Botswana.png?v=1756737911</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_kavula_art_studio</g:id>
      <title>Kavula Art Studio</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_kavula_art_studio</link>
      <description>Kavula Art Studio is a professional l art studio which Bonolo Kavula intends to use as a space for young artists to be mentored under. It can also be described as school of thought or a workshop for new artistic ideas to emerge.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Kavula_Art_Studio.png?v=1756735194</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_art_residency_centre</g:id>
      <title>Art Residency Centre</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_art_residency_centre</link>
      <description>The Art Residency Centre (ARC) is an artist-led initiative in Gaborone, Botswana, dedicated to providing space, support, and new platforms for contemporary creatives. At its core, ARC offers a residency program that provides selected artists with time, space, mentorship, and resources for a period of one to three months. The program is designed to actively contribute to the development of the artist&apos;s creative practice. Located at the Gaborone Sports &amp; Social Club, ARC&apos;s studio and reference library, &apos;The ARChive,&apos; serves as a hub for both the resident artist and the wider community. It is open to the public on Saturdays, offering opportunities for dialogue and feedback. Beyond the residency, ARC fosters a vibrant cultural ecosystem through regular film screenings, reading groups, zine workshops, exhibitions, and talks. Through a strong network of local collaborators, ARC provides invaluable networking opportunities and diverse platforms for creatives to develop, dialogue, and display their work.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Art_Residency_Centre_ARC_thumbnail.jpg?v=1758195379</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 11:06:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_desire_marea</g:id>
      <title>DESIRE MAREA</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_desire_marea</link>
      <description>Desire Marea (Duma Buyani) (b. 1991, Scottburgh, KwaZulu-Natal) is a South African artist based in Amandawe. Orphaned at six, they were raised by a supportive extended family and later discovered their lineage to Menzi Mcunu, a celebrated Durban artist and community activist. Marea studied at the National School of the Arts and earned a BA in Visual Communication from Vega School. Deeply inspired by Black culture, history, and family, their work draws on influences from artists such as Zanele Muholi, Athi-Patra Ruga, Sabelo Mlangeni, and Luvuyo Nyawose.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/DESIRE_MAREA_382b170c-a806-4a64-9cf6-aac18021d25f.png?v=1756733860</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_locus</g:id>
      <title>Locus</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_locus</link>
      <description>Locus is a contemporary art platform founded by Isa Schwartz Gesseau, dedicated to supporting artists and expanding their reach. Drawing on over twenty years of experience across art, design, and education, Isa created Locus to nurture artistic careers through curated exhibitions and participation in local and international art fairs.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Locus.png?v=1756735756</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_asisebenze_art_atelier</g:id>
      <title>Asisebenze Art Atelier</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_asisebenze_art_atelier</link>
      <description>Asisebenze Art Atelier (AAA) is a dynamic artistic hub in the heart of Johannesburg, uniquely combining an artist residency, studio spaces, and a dealership within a single ecosystem. Located in the historic Blue Plaque Heritage Building at 28 Plein Street, AAA is dedicated to nurturing and showcasing both emerging and established African creative talent. Spanning six floors, the atelier provides artists with housing, studio space, and professional mentorship, empowering them to build sustainable careers while pursuing creative freedom. The art created within Asisebenze is a direct reflection of Johannesburg&apos;s vibrant inner-city energy, with each piece telling a story of contemporary African life, culture, and identity. As a key player in the local art scene, AAA offers a direct gateway to the soul of Johannesburg&apos;s contemporary art, fostering a space where talent flourishes and careers are built</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Asisebenze_Art_Atelier_thumbnail.jpg?v=1758195632</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 12:45:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_bnap_foundation</g:id>
      <title>BNAP Foundation</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_bnap_foundation</link>
      <description>BNAP Foundation is a non-profit organisation dedicated to supporting emerging artists in South Africa through residencies, professional development, and creative exchange. Its mission is to help artists sustain their careers by offering workshops in business and artistic growth, while fostering international networking and collaboration. The foundation also runs the Blessing Ngobeni Art Prize, which supports outstanding artists under 35 working in painting, sculpture, mixed media, or performance. Recipients receive studio space, a materials budget, a stipend, mentorship, and a funded solo exhibition. BNAP Foundation is proudly sponsored by Art Angels, the Johannesburg Stock Exchange (JSE), and Everard Read Gallery Cape Town.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/BNAP_Foundation.png?v=1756732856</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 14:24:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_candice_kramer</g:id>
      <title>Candice Kramer</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_candice_kramer</link>
      <description>Candice Michelle Kramer (b. 1974, Johannesburg) is a South African painter exploring the transience of life against Johannesburg’s enduring cityscape. Working with metal surfaces, rust, and corrosion, her work references people, family photos, and maps to examine memory, time, and urban belonging. Kramer holds a BA in Fine Arts from Wits University and has exhibited at Obert Contemporary, NIROX Projects, Kalashnikovv Gallery, and 1:54 London Art Fair. Her work is in collections including Spier, Nandos, RMB, and FirstRand, and she is a resident artist at The Bag Factory, Johannesburg.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Candice_Kramer_f2c38e8f-b50c-4cf6-be08-f508e93188e2.jpg?v=1756733073</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_amg_projects</g:id>
      <title>AMG Projects</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_amg_projects</link>
      <description>Based in Lagos, Nigeria, AMG Projects is a contemporary art gallery on a mission to empower emerging African artists and curators. The gallery serves as a critical gateway for discovering game-changing talent, providing a vital platform to facilitate broader social access and global opportunities. AMG Projects curates and supports ambitious projects across diverse media, from painting and mixed-media to conceptual installations. The gallery&apos;s program is geared towards promoting curiosity and encouraging critical dialogue, with a particular focus on post-colonial and socio-political contexts in Africa. Through its dynamic exhibitions and participation in major art fairs, AMG Projects actively works to connect the continent&apos;s artists with the international art world.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/AMG_Projects_thumbnail.jpg?v=1758194632</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 10:20:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_kevin_collins</g:id>
      <title>Kevin Collins</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_kevin_collins</link>
      <description>Kevin Collins studied painting at the Michaelis School of Fine Art, UCT, under Stanley Pinker, Helmut Starke, and Cecil Skotnes. After two decades in brand communications, a health setback led him back to art, culminating in his 2003 solo exhibition The Taxonomy of Non-Endangered Species at Gallery Moja. Now working primarily in ceramics, Collins draws inspiration from travel, childhood imagery, and everyday ephemera. His works are held in collections across South Africa and internationally.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Kevin_Collins_e7894d7b-0513-40c0-8942-b55047b4cf81.jpg?v=1756735321</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_the_spaces_africa</g:id>
      <title>The Spaces Africa</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_the_spaces_africa</link>
      <description>The Spaces Africa is a dynamic platform dedicated to amplifying the presence and impact of young African galleries in the global art ecosystem. Co-founded by Gallerists Atang L.S. Arnold and Frehiwot Demissie, The Spaces Africa is a network that empowers emerging galleries, artists and art spaces by providing visibility, resources, and collaborative opportunities to help them thrive in an increasingly competitive art market. By connecting young African Galleries to the world, we aim to transform our passions into sustainable success by bridging the gaps and establishing pathways for African Contemporary Art.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/The_Spaces_Africa.png?v=1756737895</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_first_light_project</g:id>
      <title>First Light Project</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_first_light_project</link>
      <description>The First Light Project is an innovative art initiative based in Modimolle, Limpopo, where art, nature, and ophthalmology converge. Hosted within the Hope for the Blind (HFTB) eye hospital, the project integrates an exhibition space into the clinic’s design—offering post-operative patients their first visual encounter with art after cataract surgery. Curated by Johan Stegmann and Lawrence Lemaoana, the project reimagines art’s role in healing by transforming restored sight into a deeply emotional and aesthetic experience. Beyond showcasing contemporary works, it reflects on vision, perception, and renewal. Proceeds from the First Light Project, including a portion of each artwork sold, directly support subsidised eye surgeries for disadvantaged patients—merging creativity with compassion to restore both sight and hope.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/First_Light_Project.png?v=1756734324</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 14:29:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_rmb_talent_unlocked</g:id>
      <title>RMB Talent Unlocked</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_rmb_talent_unlocked</link>
      <description>RMB has an established reputation for identifying, attracting, nurturing, rewarding and celebrating exceptional talent. Liberating diverse talent to do good business for a better world is in our DNA, and we believe that ‘unlocking talent’ is key to our ongoing success. This core, ‘talent-centric’ commitment extends through all our brand partnerships, like our broad investment across the creative economy. Through RMB Talent Unlocked and in partnership with the FirstRand Foundation, we are proud to be part of the vital role that the visual arts play in our society, as both a catalyst for conversation and an archive of time.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/RMB_Talent_Unlocked.png?v=1756736934</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_azola_kingston</g:id>
      <title>Azola Kingston</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_azola_kingston</link>
      <description>Azola Kingston (b. 1994, Philadelphia; raised in Johannesburg) is a self-taught visual artist whose work is a bold celebration of Blackness. Through vibrant colour and layered composition, she affirms African stories, traditions, and voices as central to the cultural conversation. Her paintings draw beauty from community, shared rituals, and generational wisdom, creating vivid, powerful narratives of pride, presence, and resilience.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Azola_Kingston_db7d5163-fdba-4848-95d0-6661a99a088f.png?v=1756732593</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 04:25:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_amy_rusch</g:id>
      <title>Amy Rusch</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_amy_rusch</link>
      <description>Amy Rusch is a multidisciplinary artist whose practice explores vibrational mark-making through stitched thread in found plastic. Her process—cutting, stitching, heating, layering—transforms discarded materials into reflections on human and elemental time. She has exhibited widely, with recent presentations at Investec Cape Town Art Fair (2025), FNB Art Joburg (2024), and a solo with SMAC Gallery (2022). Her work has also featured at the Norval Foundation, Pretoria Art Museum, Iziko South African National Gallery, and Zeitz MOCAA.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Amy_Rusch_c3f8ca30-ebe9-4e13-adf1-23b28fbdd5b8.png?v=1756732297</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_chigozie_obi</g:id>
      <title>Chigozie Obi</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_chigozie_obi</link>
      <description>Chigozie Obi (b. 1997) is a Nigerian multidisciplinary artist whose practice reflects on human complexity, beauty, culture, women’s narratives, mental health, and healing. Her work draws from personal and collective experiences to foster connection and dialogue. She earned a Visual Arts degree from the University of Lagos in 2017 and has exhibited internationally, including 1-54 Marrakech (2025), Yenwa Gallery, Lagos (2024), AG18 Gallery, Vienna (2024), and Future Fair, New York (2023). Obi won the Access Bank Art X Prize (2021), The Future Awards Prize for Art (2021), and held a residency at Gasworks, London (2022).</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Chigozie_Obi_1f5b4ef7-e16a-4ba8-a5c4-bc23e3fae0a2.png?v=1756733214</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_fetlework_tadesse</g:id>
      <title>Fetlework Tadesse</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_fetlework_tadesse</link>
      <description>Fetlework Tadesse (Fela), born in Addis Ababa, Ethiopia, is a painter and sculptor. She holds a diploma in Fine Arts (sculpture) from Entoto Technical College (2004) and a BA in Painting from Addis Ababa University (2019). Fela has participated in numerous group exhibitions at venues including the Ethiopian National Theatre, Ethiopian National Museum, Red Door Art Gallery, and Addis Fine Art. Her debut solo exhibition was held at Findika Cultural Center in 2023, and she has exhibited internationally, including at the Addis Ababa Modern Art Museum and the Investec Cape Town Art Fair (2024). Her semi-realistic work often features self-portraits reflecting daily life, emotions, and attitudes, inspired by body gestures, fashion, and everyday patterns. Fela explores anatomy, structure, and color to convey personal narratives. She is part of the “Roots and Wings” group exhibition in Stuttgart, Germany (July 2025).</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Fetlework_Tadesse_4903dbf6-9025-4691-969f-2dae055bc800.png?v=1756734265</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_chinecherem_peace</g:id>
      <title>Chinecherem Peace</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_chinecherem_peace</link>
      <description>Chinecherem is a Nigerian textile artist whose practice reflects personal emotions and women’s lived realities while bridging tradition and innovation. She graduated as Best Student in Industrial Design (Textile) from IMT Enugu in 2017. Her work has featured in exhibitions such as the 2025 Kuenyehia Prize for Contemporary Art Exhibition, +234 Art Fair, Rele Arts Foundation’s Young Contemporaries (2025), and the 2021 My View From the Other Side exhibition at the Embassy of Spain, Abuja. She won the 2024 Kuenyehia Prize for Contemporary Art, and is a 2024 Fellow of both the Rele Arts Foundation and Kuta Art Residency.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Chinecherem_Peace_8274641a-e4bd-490e-9dce-aa2ad0c33454.png?v=1756733287</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_aleruchi_kinika</g:id>
      <title>Aleruchi Kinika</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_aleruchi_kinika</link>
      <description>Aleruchi Kinika (b.1997) is a Port Harcourt–based visual artist working in photography, writing, and drawing. Her practice preserves culture and identity through surreal, chiaroscuro-inspired storytelling that explores femininity, beauty, and fashion. Influenced by cinema and baroque light-play, Kinika conveys emotion and cultural values with dramatic intensity. She has exhibited internationally, including Polaroid x Magnum at Paris Photo Fair, and participated in residencies such as Divergence, 1952 (Lagos) and Alternative Heritage (Ibadan).</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Aleruchi_Kinika_d848762c-2a92-46d4-ab82-d890684b0a9c.png?v=1756732140</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_reem_aljeally</g:id>
      <title>Reem Aljeally</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_reem_aljeally</link>
      <description>Reem Aljeally (b. 1997) is a multidisciplinary artist and curator. She is the founder of The Muse Multi Studios (2019) and The Sudan Art Archive (2022), supporting and preserving Sudanese visual arts. Her work in painting, installation, and printmaking explores movement, space, memory, and self-image. Aljeally has exhibited internationally and currently leads the Artists Development Program at Ubuntu Art Gallery in Cairo.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Reem_Aljeally.png?v=1756736888</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_haneem_christian</g:id>
      <title>Haneem Christian</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_haneem_christian</link>
      <description>Haneem Christian is a Cape Town-based archivist and filmmaker whose lens-based practice explores Pan-African history through Queerness, centering community and African narratives. Their work has been shown at the International Cape Town Art Fair, 1-54 New York, AKAA, Latitudes, Unseen Photo Fair, and the National Portrait Gallery, London. Christian won the Pride Photo Award 2022, the Taylor Wessing National Portrait Award 2022, and a British Council Artist Grant, which funded their first docu-art film, Eyes to See, premiering at BFI Flare 2025. They have also completed a Magnum Photos residency, participated in a Nike campaign, and exhibited at the Cape Town International Art Fair.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Haneem_Christian_b03af5bb-911f-4b55-9411-765e46777656.png?v=1756734746</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_doaa_fakher</g:id>
      <title>Doaa Fakher</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_doaa_fakher</link>
      <description>Doaa Fakher (b.1992, Cairo) is an Egyptian artist whose work explores human and societal issues through distorted, anonymous figures that reflect emotional and psychological states shaped by social injustice. Working in acrylic, oil, silkscreen, and sculpture, she uses the human body as a symbol of vulnerability and resilience. Fakher holds a BA in Art Education (Cairo University, 2012) and an MA in African Arts (Helwan University, 2020). Her work has been exhibited nationally and internationally, including AKAA Paris, 1-54 Contemporary African Art Fair, and the Luxor International Painting Symposium, and is in the Museum of Modern Egyptian Art collection. She is represented by Ubuntu Art Gallery, Cairo.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Doaa_Fakher_0a860e7d-d5c3-40cd-a538-5ecf5b7040fc.png?v=1756733893</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_dina_nomena</g:id>
      <title>Dina Nomena</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_dina_nomena</link>
      <description>Dina Nomena Andriarimanjaka is a Malagasy visual artist, designer, and researcher whose transdisciplinary practice blends memory, textile, and resistance. Using embroidery, fabric remnants, and archival fragments, she explores women’s untold stories through a slow, layered process. Inspired by Malagasy heritage, matrimony, and cultural rituals, her work creates dialogue between past and present, and between individual and collective memory.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Dina_Nomena_1772862e-74b0-47e4-affd-b51300ea852b.png?v=1756733872</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_brett_rubin-3</g:id>
      <title>Brett Rubin</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_brett_rubin-3</link>
      <description>Brett Rubin (b.1982, Johannesburg) is a South African photographer and visual artist. He holds a graduate degree in Film, Media &amp; Visual Studies from the University of Cape Town (2005). Rubin has worked across fashion, design, and portraiture, notably serving as the official photographer for jazz legend Hugh Masekela from 2012 until Masekela’s passing in 2018. His work explores portraiture, landscape, and the post-colonial figure, challenging conventional photographic methods. Rubin’s work has been exhibited locally and internationally, including at Design Indaba, Edinburgh International Art and Fashion Festival, Nirox Winter Sculpture Exhibition, and Southbank Centre, London.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Brett_Rubin.png?v=1756732979</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_everard_read_gallery_johannesburg-4</g:id>
      <title>Everard Read Gallery Johannesburg</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_everard_read_gallery_johannesburg-4</link>
      <description>Founded in 1913, Everard Read is Africa&apos;s oldest and largest commercial art gallery. For over a century, it has been a premier institution in the South African art world, dedicated to showcasing the country&apos;s finest contemporary artists. With seven distinct galleries across four key locations—Johannesburg, Cape Town, London, and Franschhoek—Everard Read offers an international platform for artists from diverse backgrounds. The gallery&apos;s mission is to support artists who are committed to contemporary storytelling, exceptional craft, and the making of meaning. It champions work that interrogates both universal and Afrocentric ideas, creating contemporary icons that inspire contemplation, introspection, and awe. Everard Read is committed to the long-term representation of exceptional, established voices while continuously seeking out and nurturing the next generation of talent, ensuring a dynamic and relevant program.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Everard_Read_Gallery_Johannesburg.png?v=1756734142</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_amy-ayanda-studios</g:id>
      <title>Amy Ayanda Studios</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/amy-ayanda-studios</link>
      <description>Amy Ayanda Lester (b. 1992) is a Cape Town-based artist and musician with an Honours degree in Painting from the Michaelis School of Fine Art, UCT. Her vibrant abstract works draw inspiration from the local landscape — its flora, colours, and people — while reflecting on her family’s history of forced removal from their flower farm during Apartheid. Exploring themes of memory, loss, and beauty, Lester’s intuitive use of colour captures emotion in its immediate, playful form. In 2024, she collaborated with printmaker Roxy Kaczmarek at the David Krut Workshop, created a series of vessels with Natasha Human, and presented new works at the Latitudes Art Fair.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Amy_Ayanda_Lester_thumbnail.png?v=1759226670</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 07:14:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_brutal</g:id>
      <title>BRUTAL.</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/brutal</link>
      <description>Brutal. is a contemporary project space and gallery in Cape Town, founded by Elad Kirshenbaum and Norman O’Flynn in August 2020. Born from the challenging days of the COVID-19 pandemic, Brutal. is a multi-layered platform dedicated to a dynamic mix of emerging and established artists. More than a traditional gallery, Brutal. functions as an ecosystem, offering an artist residency, a mentorship program, and artist management facilities. Central to its identity is the BLACK CUBE project space, a direct response to the conventional &apos;white cube.&apos; This flexible space embraces the raw, unfiltered energy of the city, championing art that is experimental, edgy, and boundary-pushing. The gallery&apos;s philosophy acknowledges that while the world can be brutal, this reality is met with a spirit of being brutally creative, brutally positive, and brutally in love with art.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/img_2080.jpg?v=1759306900</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 15:11:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_khaya-malinga</g:id>
      <title>Khaya Malinga</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/khaya-malinga</link>
      <description>Khaya Malinga is a multidisciplinary artist whose practice spans painting, illustration, and digital media. His work explores themes of identity, memory, and everyday South African life, often blending realism with expressive abstraction. Malinga’s art captures intimate moments and emotional depth, reflecting his interest in storytelling through colour, form, and texture.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Khaya_Malinga_thumbnail.jpg?v=1759740958</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_linathi-makanda</g:id>
      <title>Linathi Makanda</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/linathi-makanda</link>
      <description>Linathi Makanda is a South African multidisciplinary artist from Mthatha, Eastern Cape, working across photography, fine art, and poetry. Her work explores possibility, passion, and overlooked stories, often focusing on portraiture and still life with a strong sense of vulnerability. Makanda is a member of the global Black Women Photographers community, and her photography has been recognized internationally in Vogue Italia, Color Bloc Magazine, and Cardinal Sins. Her visual project Seasons has been featured in New Plains Review and screened at the Lift-Off Online Film Festival (UK). She is also the author of the poetry collection When No One Is Watching (Odyssey Books).</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/2_3_2.png?v=1759760898</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_still-artist-residency</g:id>
      <title>STILL Artist  Residency</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/still-artist-residency</link>
      <description>Founded by artist Ayana V. Jackson, the STILL Artist Residency supports primary care-giving, LGBTQIA+, and African diasporic artists—particularly from the SADC region—through time, space, and financial support to create new work. Based in Johannesburg’s Ellis House Art Building, the three-month residency provides studio space, stipends, and a supportive community. Rooted in an ethos of care, reflection, and sustainability, STILL fosters collaboration, creative growth, and amplifies underrepresented voices in contemporary art.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/black_on_white_background_1.png?v=1761292271</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 14:47:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_bag_factory</g:id>
      <title>Bag Factory</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_bag_factory</link>
      <description>Founded in 1991, Bag Factory is a non-profit contemporary visual arts organisation in Newtown, Johannesburg. It offers studio spaces for local artists, hosts international residencies and awards, and presents exhibitions that spotlight emerging talent. Affiliated with the Triangle Network, Bag Factory fosters cultural exchange, artistic experimentation, and community engagement through its diverse programmes and outreach initiatives.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Bag_Factory.jpg?v=1761298557</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 14:09:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_warren_editions</g:id>
      <title>Warren Editions</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_warren_editions</link>
      <description>Warren Editions based in Capri as a Studios - Professional exhibitor and creative professional showcasing quality work, innovative designs, and artistic expertise in contemporary art, design, and cultural expression. Specializing in unique artistic vision and professional exhibition standards.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Warren_Editions.jpg?v=1761299549</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 05:58:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_edition__verso</g:id>
      <title>edition ~ verso</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_edition__verso</link>
      <description>edition ~ verso, founded in 2015 by master printer Sara-Aimee Verity, is a Johannesburg-based fine art print studio and publishing platform dedicated to collaboration and technical excellence. Described as a “sensitive instrument,” the studio listens, interprets, and translates artists’ ideas into print, fostering experimentation and innovation in the medium. The women-led team—Verity, Megan Rumpelt, Courteney Bentley, and Michaela Verity—works within an intimate, contemplative environment, offering a full range of printmaking techniques including intaglio, relief, collograph, chine collé, and monotype, alongside handmade paper production from studio waste. edition ~ verso has collaborated with leading artists such as Thenjiwe Nkosi, Gabrielle Goliath, Donna Kukama, Felix Shumba, and Lindokuhle Sobekwa, cultivating long-term partnerships that allow artists to explore print as an extension of their practice. The studio also runs an active internship programme, training emerging printmakers and arts professionals.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/edition___verso.png?v=1761298628</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 08:34:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_property_of_studio</g:id>
      <title>Property of Studio</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_property_of_studio</link>
      <description>Property Of Studio is a contemporary art space dedicated to championing emerging and mid-career artists across diverse mediums. Located in a vibrant cultural hub, it serves as both a space for artistic exploration and a platform for dialogue between artists, collectors, and audiences. Through curated exhibitions and collaborative projects, the studio highlights storytelling that connects personal vision with broader social and cultural themes. With a dynamic mix of physical and digital exhibitions, Property Of Studio is committed to accessibility, authenticity, and innovation—bridging the gap between artistic intent and audience engagement while redefining the contemporary art experience.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Property_of_Studio.png?v=1761299220</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 09:33:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_themba_sibeko</g:id>
      <title>Themba Sibeko</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_themba_sibeko</link>
      <description>Themba Sibeko based in Johannesburg as a Independent Artist - Professional exhibitor and creative professional showcasing quality work, innovative designs, and artistic expertise in contemporary art, design, and cultural expression. Specializing in unique artistic vision and professional exhibition standards.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Themba_Sibeko_f2d061ee-c948-433b-8c18-443bdadad15f.jpg?v=1761299481</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 06:17:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_stephen_tapestry_studio</g:id>
      <title>Stephen Tapestry Studio</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_stephen_tapestry_studio</link>
      <description>Founded in the early 1960s by Coral Stephens, Stephens Tapestry Studio is South Africa’s leading hand-weaving atelier, dedicated to preserving and advancing the art of tapestry. The studio&apos;s story is one of a creative spirit passed down as a matrilineal inheretence. From the very first artistic tapestry of a Cecil Skotness woodblock, woven by Coral&apos;s daughter Marguerite Stephens, the studio expanded its collaborators to more South African and later international artists. Known for its collaborative approach, the studio works closely with artists to translate original designs into richly textured, large-scale woven works. Each tapestry is a testament to the skill, patience, and interpretive artistry of its weavers, continuing a legacy of excellence and resilience that spans over six decades.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Stephen_Tapestry_Studio.png?v=1761299427</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 09:40:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_exhibitor_andiswa_bhungane</g:id>
      <title>Andiswa Bhungane</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/exhibitor_andiswa_bhungane</link>
      <description>Andiswa Bhungane based in Johannesburg as a Independent Artist - Professional exhibitor and creative professional showcasing quality work, innovative designs, and artistic expertise in contemporary art, design, and cultural expression. Specializing in unique artistic vision and professional exhibition standards.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/Andiswa_Bhungane_f38fd3a3-b3a3-4053-9552-6e7ac69bcdfa.jpg?v=1761298541</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 07:17:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_ecomplete-exhibition-2</g:id>
      <title>eComplete Exhibition 2</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/ecomplete-exhibition-2</link>
      <description>Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words) Gallery Bio and Statement (300 - 500 words)</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/1761553224_934d6ed3.jpg?v=1761553334</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:31:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_lucky-me</g:id>
      <title>Lucky + Me</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/lucky-me</link>
      <description>Nestled in the heart of Douala, Cameroon&apos;s bustling economic and cultural capital, Logmo + Makon stands as a dynamic institution passionately dedicated to the vibrant, complex, and evolving landscape of contemporary African art. Founded with a clear vision, we are more than just a gallery; we are a dedicated champion and a nurturing platform for the artists who are defining the continent&apos;s modern creative identity. Our core mission is to seek out, support, and actively promote a diverse roster of creators, encompassing both emerging talents taking their first audacious steps and established artists whose practices have already shaped critical conversations. We are drawn to work that is intellectually rigorous and aesthetically compelling—art that refuses to be silent. The common thread connecting our artists is a profound and critical engagement with the pressing social, political, and cultural realities of our time. Their practices delve into the intricate layers of contemporary life, from the rapid pace of urbanization and the complexities of post-colonial identity to the impacts of globalization, digital transformation, and environmental change. In a world too often reliant on singular or outdated narratives about Africa, Logmo + Makon is committed to fostering the bold artistic voices that are actively shaping new, nuanced, and multifaceted perspectives. We believe in the transformative power of art to dismantle stereotypes, challenge entrenched assumptions, and fundamentally broaden the horizons of all who engage with it. We proudly position ourselves as a vital conduit—a bridge connecting the fertile ground of local creativity in Douala and across the continent with the expansive international art scene. Through thoughtfully curated exhibitions, participation in global art fairs, and strategic partnerships with institutions, we work tirelessly to ensure that the powerful stories and unique visions of our artists resonate with a global audience. Logmo + Makon is intentionally designed as a space of dialogue, intellectual exchange, and community. We transcend the traditional &quot;white cube&quot; model to become a gathering place for artists, collectors, curators, scholars, and art lovers to connect. Here, art becomes the catalyst for essential conversations—a universal language that builds understanding and paves the way for the future of the continent.</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/1761641226_dea14e42.png?v=1761641293</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:48:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <g:id>exhibitor_test-exhibitor-1110</g:id>
      <title>test-exhibitor-1110</title>
      <link>https://latitudes-online.myshopify.com/pages/exhibitor/test-exhibitor-1110</link>
      <description>11111111111111111</description>
      <g:type>exhibitor</g:type>
      <g:image_link>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0747/7261/1293/files/1762773629_5abcea47_fd7646eb-4219-4294-8569-27af8a20b80c.png?v=1762780837</g:image_link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:28:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>